I'm with the great Ricky the great
estoy con el grande de Ricky el grande
Juan It never fails for me let's see I followed you
de Juan No falla para mí a ver te seguía
much more
mucho más
before what the [ __ ] what the [ __ ] what the [ __ ] have I
antes qué [__] qué [__] qué [__] he
done Juan what the [ __ ] have I done Juan I mean
hecho Juan qué [__] he hecho Juan o sea
Juanico Juanico is going to upload a video
Juanico Juanico va a subir un vídeo
soon a video of the gala and it just
dentro de poco un vídeo de la gala y me
became a spoiler for me in which you
acaba ser ahí un spoiler en el que le
hit it hard no wow wow what a hit you
metes fuerte no vaya vaya vaya palo la
hit it what a hit you hit the
has metido vaya palo le has metido el
best twitterer of the year How are my
mejor twittero del año Cómo está mi
people how are my people What's up What are you doing
gente cómo está mi gente Qué pasa Qué
What's up I
hacéis Qué
forgot to get the water
pasa se me ha olvidado [__] el agua
then I have to get more my
luego tengo que [__] más mi Cup
favorite Cup What's up guys Well today we
favorito Qué pasa chicos Bueno hoy
have here today we have a lot of ironing
tenemos aquí hoy tenemos mucha plancha
no Ah today we have ironing around here eh
no Ah hoy tenemos plancha por aquí eh
today we have a lot of ironing I don't know if I
hoy tenemos mucha plancha yo no sé si
can put it here to start because
puedo poner por aquí para empezar porque
in truth
en verdad
luar of course it is that in
luar claro es que en
truth it is that in truth I have put
verdad es que en verdad habber he puesto
a longer clip on the news and I
un clip más largo en el noticiero y me
imagine that in the news it will have
imagino que en el noticiero lo habrá
published it well it is not published the
publicado bueno no está publicado el
news yet we will not put it when we
noticiero todavía no lo ponemos cuando
finish the live but in the
terminemos el directo pero en el
news there will be the cules and and the
noticiero habrán los cules y y las
titties no so that they do not slap me  the
tetitas no para que no me chapen el
live so they don't catch me anything The
directo para que no me chapen nada La
Movida that com manche is burning
Movida que com manche estáa que arde
right now in trend okay I understand
ahora mismo en tendencia vale entiendo
that I understand that people are
que entiendo que la gente lo está
canceling it for a few Clip but
cancelando por unos cuantos de Clip pero
here it's not going to come out in full because here I
aquí no va a salir entero porque aquí
'm seeing
estoy viendo
54 54 seconds 54 seconds I'm seeing
54 54 segundos 54 segundos estoy viendo
here
aquí
Ah the full click I can't
Ah el click completo tampoco lo puedo
search for it right now Omega a
buscar ahora mismo Omega un
kiss because it's that I'm going to put the full clip for you
beso porque es que el clip completo os
now if anything with the
lo voy a poner ahora si acaso con con el
audio Only because I think that with the
audio Solamente porque creo que con el
audio with the audio we can
audio se con el audio nos podemos
understand each other no On the one hand there's this that
entender no Por una parte está esto que
has gone viral on Twitter this clip
se ha viralizado en Twitter este clip
haar says correct I'm speaking as I have to
haar dice correcto estoy hablando como
speak and how I have to speak
tengo que hablar y como tengo que hablar
is how I decide to speak not like you're
es como yo decido hablar no como tú me
going to tell me to speak [ __ ] or like
vas a decir que yo hable cabrón ni como
my country as I speak I'm going to speak
mi país me como hable yo voy a hablar
as I decide to speak to myself why Because
como yo decido hablarme por qué Porque
I speak as I feel like it [ __ ] feel like
yo hablo como se me da laa perra gana
something that you can't do why
algo que tú no puedes hacer por qué
Because you're a poor son of a
Porque tú eres un pobre hijo de la gran
[ __ ] you're [ __ ] I mean you're
[__] tú eres una [__] O sea tú estás
writing this and you're a poor piece of
escribiendo esto y eres un pobre de
[ __ ] okay Then you have to
[__] okay Entonces tú tienes que
literally rule and speak like a
literalmente regir y hablar como una
normal person, I don't I can speak
persona la normal yo no Yo puedo hablar
like me, like me, like I want I can
como yo como yo como yo quiera yo puedo
speak like a Mexican, like a Salvadoran,
hablar como mexicano como salvadoreño
Puerto Rican, Argentinian, I don't care
puertorriqueño argentino me da igual por
why because I have enough money
qué porque tengo el suficiente dinero
to uh do any accent and I don't give a damn
para eh hacer cualquier acento y me la
On the other hand, you don't, you go to work and you
pela En cambio tú no tú vas al trabajo y
have to say hello boss, how are you,
tienes que decir hola jefe Cómo estás
good morning, you have to say to your
Buenos días tú tienes que decirle a tu
boss, good morning, [ __ ], that's what
jefe Buenos días cabrón eso es lo que
happens, that's the difference between you and me,
pasa es la diferencia entre tú y yo
[ __ ]. That's the difference between you and me, [ __ ]. That's the difference between you and me,
cabrón Esa es la diferencia entre tú y
you go to your [ __ ] job, you
yo que tú vas a tu fucking trabajo tú
go to your [ __ ] job and you say
vas a tu fucking trabajo y y le dices
hello boss, how are you, little boss, good morning,
hola jefe qué tal jefecito Buenos días
then you have to speak
entonces tú tienes que hablar
politely every day, no, [ __ ],
educadamente todos los días yo no cabrón
I can't, I can't. I can talk however I want
Yo no pued yo no Yo puedo hablar como se
Why Because I'm rich
me dé la gana Por qué Porque soy rico
because I'm a millionaire, you're not, [ __ ]
porque soy millonario tú no lo eres
You're not, you're a piece of [ __ ]. Okay,
cabrón Tú no eres tú eres un [__] Okay
those are the ranges between you and me, [ __ ],
Esos son los rangos entre tú y yo cabrón
and that's something that you're never going to be able to
y eso es algo que tú nunca vas a llegar
do like me, you have to have already two,
a hacer como yo tienes que ha ya dos
fitness, he hasn't gotten inside
fitness no se ha eh metido dentro del
Comanche's body, let's see The Move. It's that
cuerpo de Comanche a ver La Movida Es
later, let's see, I'm going to try to catch him from the
que luego a ver voy a intentar cogerlo
news but I'm going to put only
del noticiero pero voy a poner solamente
audio okay I'm going to put only audio
audio vale voy a poner solamente audio
because girls in thongs and stuff are on there he
porque salen chicas en tanga y demás él
's watching Instagram I don't know if girls in
está viendo Instagram no sé si chicas en
thongs something would happen cleavage and girls in
tanga pasaría algo escotes y chicas en
thongs something happens on YouTube
tanga pasa algo en YouTube
just in case we put the audio and that's it
por si acaso ponemos el audio y ya está
No better no but well yes it's true
No mejor no pero bueno sí que es verdad
that Comanche's vocabulary
que el vocabulario de
is there okay it's there the
Comanche está ahí vale está ahí la
truth is that I don't know what's wrong with him these
verdad es que no sé qué le pasa estos
days you know that Comanche well had
días ya sabéis que Comanche pues tuvo
his little problems no and I imagine that the
sus problemillas no y me imagino que el
Stream accentuates it and ends up
Stream lo acentúa y lo termina
accentuating it and I don't know the truth I don't know
acentuando y no sé yo la verdad no sé yo
if he's interested in being on Stream and being like that the
si le interesa est en Stream y estar así
truth is he's gone quite crazy
verdad se le ha ido bastante la la olla
here in these comments Look I'll
aquí en estos comentarios Mira os lo
put it in audio okay let's listen to it
pongo en audio vale lo vamos a escuchar
in
en
audio sweet a
audio dulce un
kiss I had already I had already
beso yo ya me había yo ya me había
put myself Hot I said I'm going to eat this
puesto Hot yo dije me voy a comer este
ass really nice I'm going to eat it I'm going to
culo bien rico se lo voy a comer se lo
suck it and I'm going to dedicate myself
voy a mamar y la voy a dediar
entirely I had already put myself but
enteramente yo ya me había puesto pero
I can't I can't because she has a
yo no puedo yo no puedo porque tiene
husband eh dude just so you know if you're
esposo eh pana que sepas si me estás
watching me dude for you look  you for you out of
viendo pana por ti mira por ti por ti
respect for you I'm not going to eat
por respeto a ti no le voy a comer el
your girlfriend's ass okay He's looking at
culo a a tu novia okay Está viendo el
a girl's Instagram and well she gets hot
Instagram de una chica y bueno se pone
bull starts saying things to him
calent torro empieza a decirle cosas
then it turns out the girl has a partner
luego resulta que la chica tiene pareja
and she starts saying these things that you
y se pone a a decir estas cosas que
're seeing I'm not going to eat
estáis viendo no le voy a comer el culo
your girlfriend's ass for you man well for him and
a tu novia por ti hombre bueno por él y
because maybe she doesn't want to either out of
porque a lo mejor ella tampoco quiere
respect for you my uncle says but
comche por respeto a ti mi tío dice pero
if that guy didn't exist I'm
si ese cabrón no existiera yo soy un
dangerous who goes and eats her ass and
peligroso que va y le come el culo y le
eats her tits and everything
com el too las tetas y todo
because to think that there are 200
que porque el pensar que están 200
people here watching me are the
personas aquí viendome mi son reales los
audios real Yeah yeah I mean if it's Stream
audios Sí sí O sea si es que es Stream
also I'm not putting the Stream
además no os estoy poniendo el Stream
because the images are coming out and and
porque están saliendo las imágenes y y
Well then on the news they are
Bueno luego en el noticiero están sin
uncensored I mean uncensored sorry censored I'm getting a
censurar o sea sin censurar perdón
little scared wait I'm
censuradas me me poquito de susto espera
going to I'm going to mute myself for a moment
me voy a me voy a mutear un momentito
I'm going to go to the bathroom okay Come on come on vo to the
voy a ir al baño okay Dale dale vo al
bathroom but yes yes you're going to go touch yourself and that
baño pero si si vas a ir a tocarte y eso
tell me so I can go to the bathroom together and we
dime para yo también ir al baño juntos y
do it
lo hacemos
together I was hotter with the whip
juntos estaba más caliente con latigazo
in the ear it's not hotter than the
en la oreja no está más caliente que el
cicer a
cicer un
bingo I think I don't think I'm not going to
bingo creo que no creo que no voy a
touch myself
tocarse
then he has some suitor around
entonces tiene alguna pretendienta por
here Comanche didn't
aquí El Comanche no me
tell me what he what I'm coming back I'm coming back
dijo el qué elé el qué Ya vengo ya vengo
well people people I don't know what's going on
bueno gente gente yo no sé qué pasa
people I I don't know what the
gente
[ __ ] I don't know what the [ __ ]
yo yo no sé qué [__] yo no sé qué [__]
is going on people but out of nowhere
está pasando gente pero de la nada salen
these little gems come out that's why one lives to make
estas joyitas así por eso uno vive por
these little gems live
hacer estas joyitas en directo
Ah I don't know I don't know
Ah no sé no sé
eh I don't know if he's playing with me if he
eh yo no sé si está jugando conmigo si
's telling the truth but I have my
está diciendo la verdad pero yo yo tengo
dick really hard right now I have it good I have I'm really turned on right now eh I don't know no s we're here talking about sex he says he wants me to put it on all fours that he wants to suck my penis but I don't understand why you're
pene pero yo no entiendo por qué estáis
making those comments on Stream I
haciendo esos comentarios en Stream o
mean the girls what are you saying to him per
sea las chicas qué le están diciendo per
clear he cut me off here the
claro me ha cortado aquí lugar las
parts of the things that he's
partes de de las cosas que él está
saying but I would have loved to see
diciendo pero me hubiera encantado ver
the chat and the people who are entering if they
el chat y la gente que está entrando si
're following along If they're
le está siguiendo el rollo Si están
playing with him
jugando con él
look here is when he starts entering the
mira aquí es cuando se pone a entrar en
girl's Instagram  this Uy uy uy uy
el Instagram de la chica esta Uy uy uy
uy uuuuuuy let's see let's see let's see let's
uy uy uuuuuuy a ver a ver a ver a ver a
see Uy but she doesn't follow me she doesn't follow me she
ver Uy pero no me sigue no me sigue
wants to be my girlfriend and she doesn't follow me
quiere ser mi novia y no me sigue la
Lisa has a nice ass really
lisa tiene buen culo la verdad
Oh she has nice tits too let's
Ay tiene buenas tetas
see Sergio Sergio sent me
también a ver Sergio Sergio me envió
Sergio sent me Out of control I'm gonna give you
Sergio me envió Sin Control te voy a dar
that ass
ese culo te
with you Man then I'm gonna give you this is he
con Man desp te voy aumar esto es é
singing eh he's
cantando eh es é
singing e e this is
cantando e e esto es perreo
slow twerking a really bloody twerking that ass
lento un perreo bien sangriento ese culo
mamacita I wanna give it to you inside
mamacita Yo quiero darte por dentro
Ah it's put Call a girl Look at this
Ah se pone Llamar a una chica Mira este
yes I can
sí os lo puedo
play it for you call a girl on the phone and
poner llama a una chica por teléfono y
look
mira
manche Hello Hello
manche Hola Hola
[Music]
[Música]
tell me hello learned very new
dime hola aprendió muy nueva streamer
favorite
favorita menor que
streamer under three Hello eh it's an outbreak it could be an outbreak it couldn't be an outbreak not perfectly Uy look really today I was trying today I was trying about this girl on the news you roasted roasted weed man I mean I didn't know her I was trying today on the
conocía lo Estuve tratando hoy en el
news she's an influencer you're an
noti es una influencer tú es una
influencer who begs I mean it went
influencer que suplica o sea se hizo
viral Because  begs someone to
viral Porque suplica alguien que la
support her and she asks with all the
mantenga y lo pide con todas la
need in the world because she doesn't want to
necesidad del mundo porque no quiere
work, she doesn't like to work, she wouldn't
trabajar que no le gusta trabajar no
do this if it weren't really urgent,
haría esto si no fuera realmente urgente
no, I wouldn't do this if it weren't
yo no Yo no haría esto si no fuera
really urgent, okay, I need
realmente urgente vale Necesito que
someone to support me, I need someone to
alguien me mantenga Necesito que alguien
support me because I don't like to work, she does
me mantenga porque no me gusta trabajar
n't like to no, I feel like I was born
que no le gusta no Yo siento que nací
for something else, I don't know, I need a
para otra cosa no sé necesito una
solution, it's very difficult, all of this, people,
solución es muy difícil todo esto gente
please, enough, of course, and, well, then
por favor basta claro y y Bueno luego ya
I'll
me
crack up last, new, eh, well, this is the
descojono últimos nuevo eh Bueno est es
sister, look, the sister who
la hermana fíjate la hermana que no
had absolutely nothing to do with it, okay, and it
tenía absolutamente nada que ver vale Y
was the news that made it
era la noticia por la que se ha
viral, no, but this video had a
viralizado no pero es que este vídeo Me
huge impact on me, you see, this, this had a
impactó demasiado verás este este me
huge impact on me, you
impactó demasiado en cualquier momento
could say, well, from now on,
se podría decir Bueno A partir de ahora
the current currency
la moneda corriente
is the earth and it's worth it at
es la tierra y vale en cualquier momento
any moment, you could say, Hey,
en cualquier momento se podría decir Oye
look, from now on, this is like
pues mira A partir de ahora esto es como
when we went from the PS to the Euro, okay, hey,
cuando pasamos de la PS al Euro vale oye
look, from now on, the
pues mira A partir de ahora la moneda
common currency of the entire planet is going to be the
común de todo el planeta va a ser la
earth, go for the Play 5, a bigger handful,
tierra vaj a por la Play 5 un puñado más
okay, you're going to buy a
grande vale vas a comprarte una
bicycle, a bag of
bicicleta una bolsa de
earth, you're going to buy a Ferrari, seven
tierra vas a comprarte un Ferrari siete
bags of fencing or so incredible
sacos de cercol o sea increíble
incredible reasoning
increíble razonamiento se solucionarían
many lives would be saved of course and the problem is there the
muchas vidas claro y el problema hay el
problem is there as I said in the
problema lo tiene como he dicho en el
news Whoever lives in a skyscraper
noticiero El que viva en un rasca cielo
No that one has nothing What does he
No ese no tiene nada Qué
say oh I forgot to put the tweet you
dice ay se me olvidó meter el tweet tú
forgot to put the tweet luare Oh how
se me olvidó meter el tweet luare Oh qué
angry I forgot to put it in man in the
coraje se me olvidó meterse t tío en el
news there everyone would start
noti ahí todo el mundo se pondría a
collecting land and of course there I will donate to you
recolectar tierra y claro ahí sí te dono
old man there I would donate not even with that I would
viejo ahí sí me donaría ni con esa me
donate to me surely not even with that you would
donaría seguramente ni con esa os
keep all the land for yourselves
quedaríais tod tierra para ustedes
surely only those
seguro solamente saldrían beneficiados
who live in a field would benefit those who have
los que viven en un campo los que tienen
more land because in an apartment I
más terreno porque yo en un departamento
am not the owner of any
no soy dueña de ninguna
land of course those who have those who have land would benefit more
tierra claro saldrían más beneficiados
in that change
en ese cambio los que tienen los que
basically Of course She
tienen tierras básicamente Claro Ella
for example lives in an apartment and
por ejemplo vive en un apartamento y
surely she has rented it at least I mean
Seguramente se ha alquilado si quiera o
if she had Ah a pot she couldn't
sea si tuviera Ah una maseta no podría
take the land from the apartment either
[__] la tierra tampoco del apartamento
okay I mean she wouldn't have anything she would have to
vale O sea ella no tendría nada tendría
ask for land Prada or go into a
que pedir tierra Prada o meterse en un
neighbor you understand she would have to go out and
un vecino entendés tendría que salir a
buy it or  steal it from a park
comprarla o a robarla a un parque a
steal it from a
robarla a un
park is that I just imagined it
parque es que me la acabo de imaginar
gachi I just imagined her stealing
gachi Me la acabo de imaginar robando
land in a park I swear And well
tierra en un parque te lo juro Y bueno
people are criticizing Comanche
pues la gente está criticando a Comanche
and Comanche has started fighting with
y Comanche se ha vuelo a pelearse con
twitterers let's see
con twitteros a ver
here let's see my son How do you
aquí a ver hijo mío Cómo se
notice in a girl who was with
nota en una chica que se le estaba a
Comanche and told him that she was going to eat
Comanche y le decía que le iba a comer
everything and that she wanted him to eat her
todo y que quería que él le comiera el
clot and it seems that the other one got
clo y parece que el otro se calentó de
too heated let's see if a kid has
más claro a ver si si un chaval se ha
showered himself in gasoline and you bring her a
duchado en gasolina y tú la acercas un
lighter close by in the two is
mechero por ahí cerquita en el dos está
Comanche's response In which two
la respuesta de Comanche En cuál dos
[ __ ] in the live one or in the
cabrón en el del directo o en el de
noti Don't tell me you had this around here
noti No me digas que tenías tú por aquí
dude Don't tell me you had it around here or
tío No me digas que lo tenías por aquí o
where direct with manche I mean but I
dónde directo con manche o sea pero yo
can put the com manche clis here let's see let's see let's
puedo poner aquí los clí de com
see Put the two of the live one let's see click
ver Pon el dos del directo a ver click
with text I understand that we have already seen it
con texto entiendo que ya lo hemos visto
no Oh no
no Ah
and I already  there I had already put
no y ya me había yo ya me había puesto
Hot I said no I can't see asses
Hot yo dije no no puedo ver culos
luares I can't see mojinos or if I can
luares no puedo ver mojinos o si puedo
see
ver
mojinos I can't see mojinos I'm going to eat
mojinos no puedo ver mojinos voy a comer
this ass really rich I know this click is
este culo bien rico se lo este click es
the one from
el de
yesterday Then there is the clip of Calling the
ayer Luego está el clip de Llamando a la
poor people that we have seen it
gente pobre que lo hemos visto
and Comanche's response okay let's
y la respuesta de Comanche vale vamos a
see the
ver la
response is processing is processing is processed I ca
respuesta está
n't see it is
processed no puedo verlo está
processed goodbye to monetization man
processed adiós a la monetización hombre
I don't know what's going on There with a little ass I
Yo no sé qué pasa Ahí con un culillo la
really do
verdad
n't know What problem can there be with a little
no sé Qué problema puede haber con un
ass out there Inc Sky let's see with a little
culete por ahí Inc Sky a ver con un
ass I don't know but oh well luare then the
culete no sé pero bueno luare luego el
extract censored censored the gte
extracto censuro censur los gte
[ __ ] Hey luare wanted to stick an
[__] Oye que luare quería meterme ahí un
ass in my
culo por la
face there I've been putting this there censored for a while now you ca
cara llevo un rato poniendo ahí
n't see Comanche's response you ca
censurado este no se ve la respuesta de
n't
Comanche no se
see
ve
if you put VPN it lets you see it I don't have
si pones VPN te deja verlo no tengo
VPN today is not dinner dude today is not
VPN hoy no s cena tío hoy no s
dinner [ __ ] let's see if it loads
cena [__] a ver si me carga
you let's see if it loads me processing processing
tú a ver si me a ver si me carga
processing what goes on what goes on it doesn't load a
processing que va que va que no carga un
minute Come on minute family says places
minuto Dale minuto familia dice lugares
that  let's give him a minute what do we do we'll
que le demos un minuto qué hacemos se lo
give it to him grandpa and Fran Well he was better
damos abuelo y Fran Pues estaba mejor
today I saw he was live
hoy lo he visto que ha estado en directo
with Pablo I think
con el Pablo
today I think he was live with
creo hoy creo que estado en directo con
Pablo if it wasn't
el Pablo si no era
recorded I told him to come here and you
grabado le dije que viniera por aquí y
abandoned me No man it's just that
me ha abandonado tú No hombre es que
when I told him he was
cuando se lo dije estaba
[Music]
[Música]
freshly freshly rolled around in the sky
recién recién revolcado por el cielo
freshly
recién
rolled around Dalas made a video
revolcado Dalas le ha hecho un vídeo
Comanche I don't believe it
Comanche no lo creo
no I don't believe it
no no lo
Well make me a nice coffee Oh make me
Bueno me hace un cafel lillo Ay me hace
a nice coffee in the meantime
un cafel lillo de mientras
no
no
Well look luare when we upload this
Pues mira luare cuando subamos este
excerpt you have to censor your ass and
extracto tienes que censurar el culo y
cut this wait he was live
recortar esta espera estaba en directo
today with Pablo and Cristina
hoy con Pablo y Cristina
no what date are you going to the sanctuary Javi in the
no qué fecha te vas al santuario Javi a
end at the end of the
final al final de
month if not if not I'll sell the
mes si no si no vendo el
ticket Jai look at it on sur news
billete Jai que lo mires en sur news
[ __ ] cristalitos they all don't give a damn about me Now
[__] cristalitos me la pelan todos Ya
[ __ ] cristalitos they all don't give a damn about me Now they're acting like
[__] cristalitos me la pelan todos ya
vigilantes on [ __ ]
se la dan de justicieros en el fucking
Twitter and I'm going to shoot them all for
Twitter y a todos les voy a dar bala por
[ __ ] [ __ ] cristalitos they all don't give a damn about me Now [ __ ] cristalitos they all don't
mamones [__] cristalitos me la pelan
give a damn about me
todos Ya [__] cristalitos me la pegan
Now they're  of vigilantes on
todos Ya se la dan de justicieros en el
[ __ ] Twitter and I'm going to shoot you all
fucking Twitter y a todos les voy a dar
for being [ __ ] and jerks sons of
bala por cabrones y mamones hijos de la
[ __ ] all the sons
gran [__] me la pelean todos los hijos
of [ __ ] that see me fight me you sons of [ __ ]
de [__] que me ven ustedes hijo de [__]
don't know anything what to do So I go and
no saben Nada de qué hacer Así que voy y
kill you I'll kill you son of a [ __ ] buy yourself
los mato te mato hijo de [__] cómprate
a life stop coming to my [ __ ]
una vida deja de venir a mis [__]
crimes And this is not for you [ __ ] okay
delitos Y esto no para ti cabrón okay
Okay you [ __ ] see my live is over 18 I don't
Okay de [__] ves mi directo es más 18 no
want a kid as son of a [ __ ] as you
quiero un niño tan hijo de [__] como tú
Better rock go see what to do son of a [ __ ]
Mejor mecer ve que hacer hijo de [__]
get a life a [ __ ] job
consigue t una vida un [__] trabajo
I'm making millions while I see
estoy facturando millones mientras veo
asses and I see ideas too and you don't know what's
culos y veo deas también y no sabes qué
gonna happen but what I'm gonna
va a pasar pero lo que sí que voy a
do is
hacer e
[Music]
[Música]
[ __ ] [ __ ] me those on
[__] mme la [__] los de
Twitter Oh mom [ __ ] me those on
Twitter Ay mam la [__] los de
Twitter [ __ ] me [ __ ] crystals I don't
Twitter me la [__] [__] cristalitos me
care about you all A couple of dicks you're all
valen todos Un par de pijas todos son
idiots who don't know humor
unos [__] que no saben de humor
sons of [ __ ] I'm gonna keep
hijos de la gran [__] voy a seguir
seeing asses I don't care about anything
viendo culos me vale verdad todo lo que
you say Okay sons of [ __ ] You're
digan ustedes Okay hijos de [__] Son
[ __ ] kids no  you have to do
unos [__] niños no tienen que hacer
get a life or better yet a [ __ ]
consíganse una vida o mejor un [__]
job get out of your house stop looking at your
trabajo salgan de su casa deja de ver el
phone [ __ ] and start billing [ __ ]
teléfono cabrón y ponte a facturar [__]
cristalitos meme my ass and see if on
cristalitos meme la [__] ya ver si en
the street you have the balls to say what I
la calle tenes dos huevos de decir lo
say on Twitter son of a [ __ ] Put up
que decí en Twitter hijo de [__] Ponte
a profile picture of yourself and not of
una foto de perfil tuya y que no sea de
another [ __ ] streamer son of a
otro fucking streamer hijo de la gran
[ __ ] [ __ ] cristalitos mme in the dick
[__] [__] cristalitos mme en la [__]
already [ __ ] cristalitos mmen in the dick already
ya [__] cristalitos mmen en la [__] ya
and they [ __ ] me up for anything I can no longer
y me funan por cualquier cosa yo ya no
dedicate myself to the world of streaming
me puedo dedicar al mundo del streaming
I have it or whatever but that song He
yo tengo o sea pero esa canción La ha
made it improvised live or he
hecho improvisada en directo o la ha
recorded it he edited it and then he
grabado la ha editado y luego la ha
uploaded it let's see I think it's an outbreak eh with
subido a ver creo que es un brote eh con
all Respect in the world I mean we're
todo Respeto del mundo o sea nos estamos
laughing and such because of the situation Because we are
riendo y tal por la situación Porque
here no but I think it's an
estamos aquí no pero creo que es un
outbreak I think it's an outbreak I
brote creo que es un brote Me da me da
feel like it's an outbreak I have to
la sensación que es un brote tengo que
take the leap into music and I'm
dar el Salto a la música y estoy
practicing to take the leap into
practicando para dar el Salto a la
music but because of you maybe I wo
música pero por tu culpa a lo mejor yo
n't be able to take the leap into
ya no voy a poder dar el Salto a la
music and I'll have to stay with the
música y me tendré que quedar con las
funas you want That Adri well no let's go let's
funas tú quieres Eso Adri bueno no vamos
talk to Lisa more about sex and
vamos a hablar con la lisa más de sexo y
all that so they keep getting mad on
todo eso para que se sigan enojando en
Twitter about the shitty crystals I'm going to
Twitter los cristalitos de [__] voy a
put some coffee in the coffee maker eh I
voy a ponerme un café en la cafetera eh
mean I'm listening to the clip but I'm
o sea Estoy escuchando el clip pero me
going to put some coffee in the coffee maker
voy a poner un café en la cafetera
while I listen This is literally an outbreak eh
mientras que escucho Esto sí es un brote
let's keep talking
literalmente eh vamos a seguir hablando
there on discord about [ __ ] about her
ahí en discord de de pendejada de su
ass we're going to talk about her ass her
culo vamos a hablar de su culo de sus
tits her [ __ ] everything about everything she
tetas de su [__] de todo de todo lo
likes about everything she
que le gusta a ella de todo lo que le
likes to be done to her so the
gusta que le hagan para que se enojen
people on Twitter get madder so they get madder
más los de Twitter para que se enojen
and keep getting madder mom I want
más y se sigan enojando más mam Quiero
a couple of [ __ ] to suck me off
un par de [__] para que me lo mamen
I want a couple of [ __ ] to
Quiero un par de [__] para que me lo
suck me off I want a couple of [ __ ] to
mamen Quiero un par de [__] para que me
suck me off suck my penis suck my
lo mamen me chupen el pene me chupen el
penis I like how cho the pz the pz the
pene me gusta como cho el pz el pz el el
p inspiration I need to see a really
p inspiración Necesito ver un culo bien
nice ass to get inspired to release a song
rico para inspirarme sacar una canción
about an ass like that sucking ass [ __ ] it
de un culo así de chupar culo cabrón
has  an ass that I want to eat
tiene un toto que se lo quiero comer la
Lalisa has an ass that I want to
lalisa tiene un toto que se lo quiero
eat Lalisa has an ass that I
comer la lalisa tiene un toto que se lo
want to eat I want to spank it I
quiero comer se lo quiero azotar se lo
want to eat it Lalisa has an ass that I
quiero comer la lalisa tiene un toto que
want to eat Lalisa has an
se lo quiero comer la lalisa tiene un
ass that I want to eat I want to
toto que se lo quiero comer se lo quiero
spank it damn that ass is
azotar [__] ma ese totito está
big babe I wanna [ __ ] you in that
grandote mamacita quiero darte por el
ass you got Go on move it Go on move that ass Go on move that
culo que tienes Dale mueve toto Dale
ass Go on move that ass Go on move that tos Go on move tos up down up down her
ese culo muéveme ese culo Dale dale
tit is so
to to arriba abajo arriba abajo sueta
yummy her tit is so
rica está su teta qué rica está su teta
yummy her tit is so yummy Come
qué rica está su teta qué rica está su
on mama my mother I'm
teta Dale mamacita mi madre Me estoy
selling myself hot she's really hot she has
vendo buena que está bien rica que tiene
an incredible ass and
un culo increíble y unas tetas
incredible tits oh my god they just
increíbles Dios mío Santo apenas me
flagged me yesterday
funaron ayer
dude they just flagged me yesterday after 29
cabrón me funaron apenas ayer con 29
days of doing this [ __ ] they just flagged me
días haciendo esta pendejada me funaron
yesterday I mean and this yesterday
ayer apenas o sea y esto que lo de ayer
yesterday was
lo de ayer fue
soft we've done things  worse in the
soft hemos hecho cosas peores en los de
previous live people if you really
anterior directo gente si de verdad me
want to deceive me I invite you to watch my 29
quieren funar Los invito a ver mis 29
previous live streams There are worse things
directos anteriores í Hay cosas peores
than yesterday yesterday was soft
que lo de ayer lo de ayer fue soft lo de
yesterday was
ayer fue
soft soft of
soft soft of
soft
soft
context of the funa Real yesterday the
contexto de la funa Real ayer el más
calmest yesterday was the
tranqui s ayer fue el más
calmest context of the funa adana Look, I'll
tranqui contexto de la funa adana Mira
explain on Twitter an idiot who
te explico en Twitter un un estúpido que
will never grow on Twitch who is a
nunca va a crecer en Twitch que es un
moralist who thinks he
moralista que se cree
thinks that by deceiving me he will grow
que se cree que por funar me va a crecer
on Twitch that literally all of his
en Twitch que literalmente todos sus
tweets have two likes but the one that
tweets tienen dos likes pero el que me
[ __ ] me has a lot of like because obviously of
fó tiene muchos like porque obviamente
course win win win win honey son
claro gana gana gana gana de miel hijo
of a [ __ ] I mean win
de [__] o sea gana
was Green hair eh the one with the most
fue Green hair eh el que tiene muchos
likes refers to Green hair I think I think
likes se refiere a Green hair creo Creo
the click is that mother of me
que el click es ese madre mí
eh put put the clip where I said that
eh puso puso el clip donde yo decía que
Lisa's ass was really good and
estaba bien bueno ese culo de la lisa y
Lisa had come Ah tell me and I want you to
la lisa había venido Ah decirme e quiero
see my Instagram I want you to see me
que veas mi Instagram quiero que me veas
because I want I want you to suck my
porque quiero quiero que me [__] el
ass so I went and said oh yeah
culo entonces yo fui y le dije ah sí
your ass is good I love your ass and I
Está bueno tu culo me encanta tu culo y
want to suck it but the  Lisa had
quiero mamártelo pero la lisa había
come here before to put it to me in the
venido antes a ponérmelo aquí en en el
chat and she said Hey I want you to see my
chat me puso Oye quiero que veas mi
Instagram and I want you to suck my ass
Instagram y quiero que me [__] el culo
eh Are you going to suck it or not and I said let's
eh Me lo vas a mamar o no y yo le dice a
see I want to see your Instagram to see if
ver quiero ver tu Instagram para ver si
it's true that she has a nice ass and she
es cierto que tiene buen culo y me lo
sent it to me and I saw it live and I said that
pasó y yo lo vi en directo y dije que
her ass was good and that's it And that's
estaba bueno su culo y ya está Y eso es
what I did I mean no
lo que yo hice o sea no
boo well eh Right now we're going to talk to
buo bueno eh Ahorita vamos a hablar con
her because we're going to want to continue we
ella porque vamos queremos seguir
want she was also upset that the
queremos ella también le molestó que los
crystal boys got mad so she
niños cristalitos se enojaran entonces
told me you know what eh I told her Hey let's
me dijo sabes qué eh yo le dije Oye
make a call if you want at
hagamos una llamada si quieres en la
night and we keep giving it to her the
noche y y le seguimos dando Caña los
crystal boys and she said okay okay let's
cristalitos y me dijo vale vale vamos a
make a call and we'll do some
hacer una llamada y hacemos ahí hacemos
[ __ ] there and she's going to come over
ahí pendejadas y ahorita va a venir ella
in 20 minutes she's coming over and we're going to be
en 20 minutos viene y vamos a estar
doing [ __ ] there talking about sex
haciendo ahí pendejadas hablando de sexo
and talking about everything and so that the
y hablando de todo y para que se sigan
shitty crystal boys keep getting mad
enojando los niños cristalitos de [__]
the frustrated boys we've literally
los niños frustrados literalmente
been doing we've been doing
llevamos haciendo llevamos haciendo
worse things these past 26 days and until
cosas peores estos 26 días y hasta
just yesterday but that's like  speak
apenas ayer pero eso eso en plan habla
well of the community I'll tell you
bien de la comunidad te voy a decir por
why Because we are already creating a
qué Porque ya estamos creando una
community baa my grandfather W who no longer
comunidad baa mi abuelo W que ya le está
gives a [ __ ] what I do
valiendo [__] lo que yo haga
simply What's up [ __ ] have you
simplemente Qué pasa cabrones habéis
released cli no more eh Let's see the cli Eh
sacado cli ya no eh A ver el cli Eh
well Green hair was not the one who screwed it
bueno Green hair no fue el que lo fó
Green hair put the click this one
Green hair puso el click este del que
we saw at the beginning no it was the one about him
hemos visto al principio no que era lo
being a millionaire and all that
del lo de que era millonario y demás
okay
vale
And and I don't know what twitterers are
Y y no sé de qué twitteros están
talking about I imagine that they were the two that
hablando Me imagino que eran los dos que
I caught before they are coming because they
he cogido antes están viniendo porque le
like the content they like what happens
gusta el contenido le gusta lo que pasa
and they know that I am not a bad person that
y saben que yo no soy mala persona que
I only do it to give them content
yo solo lo hago por por darles contenido
and I don't do it because I mean with Lisa
y no lo hago porque o sea yo con la lisa
Eh I talk when I'm off the
Eh hablo yo cuando estoy fuera de la
song it was catchy eh things
canción estaba pegadiza eh las cosas
as they are
como son
eh the song was catchy eh live
eh la canción estaba pegadiza eh directo
with Lisa let's see I'm with this
con la lisa a ver estoy con esto
wait me when I'm off
espérate yo cuando estoy fuera de
live with Lisa I I talk normal
directo con la lisa yo yo hablo normal
people I talk to her normally like a
gente yo hablo con ella normal como un
man like a gentleman what happens is that
hombre como un caballero lo que pasa es
live Well I know the  kids
que en directo Pues yo yo sé a los niños
like this content they like that
les gusta este contenido les gusta esa
[ __ ] So I tell her [ __ ]
pendejada Entonces yo le digo pendejadas
because live Obviously she
a ella porque en directo Obviamente le
likes it she likes it but outside of live
gusta le gusta pero yo fuera de directo
with Lisa from Hey How Are You All good
con la lisa de Oye Cómo estás Todo bien
I don't tell her off live Lisa I
Yo no le digo fuera directo la lisa te
want to suck your ass I want to grope you I
quiero chupar el culo te quiero manosear
want to put my hands on you I love you no
te quiero meter las manos te quiero no
off live I don't tell her that people I mean
fuera directo no le digo eso gente O sea
here I come because I do it because I
aquí vengo porque lo hago porque porque
want you all to laugh and she laughs too and we all laugh and we all
quiero que ustedes se rían y ella
laugh and nobody gets mad but
nos reímos todos y nadie se enoja pero
the kids on Instagram do get mad
los niños de Instagram sí se enojan
because they're [ __ ] they're
porque son unos [__] son unos
[ __ ] So that's it FES Sergio's mom,
[__] Entonces ya está FES la mamá de
dude, that was more funable
Sergio cabrón eso estaba más funable
Sergio's mom was more funable
la mamá de Sergio estaba más funable
dude Look So that's it people, we're not
cabrón Mira Entonces ya está gente ya no
going to talk about the subject anymore because today
vamos a hablar más del tema porque hoy
we came to turn you guys on I
venimos a poner los cachondos a ustedes
just covered her with my camera I can't
justo la tapé con mi cámara no puedo
move my camera even a little bit I'm
mover mi cámara ni un poquito así de
saying it clearly eh we're going to talk about sex
claro lo digo eh os a hablar de sexo
because that's what you like and to screw
porque es lo que les gusta y a [__] a
the crystal kids of Twitter
los niños cristalitos de de Twitter
because we know that that also
porque sabemos que también eso les
turns you on then  we came to a to add
emperra entonces venimos a a a ponerle
morbidity to this not to curse the
morb a esto no para juder más a los
crystal children more no
niños cristalitos no
Yes to give them content also so
Sí para dar les contenido también para
that they continue to fund us No yes they
que nos sigan fundando No sí que nos
fund us together Look, the truth is
funden juntos Mira a ver la verdad es
that it was a joke
que fuera cachondeo
eh I know what he's saying about it being
eh sé que está diciendo lo de que es
a show okay I understand that what he's
un show vale entiendo que lo que está
saying is that it's a show but but
diciendo es que es un show pero pero hay
there is a behavior there that was not what he
ahí un comportamiento que no era el que
had for example the day he came to the
tenía por ejemplo el día que vino a la
interview
entrevista
finally making good content El Comanche
por fin hace buen contenido El Comanche
man no I hope that one of his
hombre no Espero que alguien de sus
friends, one of those who are close to him,
amigos de los que están cerca de él pues
take care of him and take a look at him
le le cuiden y le echen un vistazo
I hope that things stay like that or that's it
Espero que se quede la cosa en o ya está
or that it's nothing
o que no sea nada
okay are you seriously telling me that they're going
vale me estás diciendo en serio que van
to funnare Comanche for one comment
a funar a Comanche por uno comentario
that is the day to day of socas and everyone
que es el día a día de socas y todos le
laughs at his jokes or Juan when he talked
ríen las gracias o de Juan cuando habló
about his bed
de su cama
no Let's see, it's not funnable, I don't see it, let's
no A ver no es funable yo no lo veo a
see, I don't see it funnable like
ver yo no lo veo funable como
m a little cringe the attitude putting yourself
m un poco cringe la actitud ponerte en
live you know what I'm telling you
directo sabes lo que te digo
one thing is that you're making
a una cosa es que tú estés haciendo un
Hot content, no that I  I imagine that what he
contenido Hot no que me imagino que lo
is justifying is that he is
que está justificando es que está
making Hot content and at a
haciendo un contenido Hot y en un
given moment well you are talking about sex
momento dado pues estás hablando de sexo
and such But to say just to say they suck my [ __ ] they
Y tal Pero decir por decir me la maman
suck my dick my such or I mean I don't know
me la chupan mi [__] mi tal o sea no sé
I don't see it I don't see it that it is part
no lo veo yo no lo veo yo que sea parte
of the script outline you understand
de la escaleta del guion me entiendes
another thing is the bad vocabulary of the
otra cosa es el mal vocabulario del
choca of course I have already criticized him
choca por supuesto yo ya lo he criticado
on many occasions but I understand that it
en muchas ocasiones pero entiendo que
is also his character But it is not the
también es su personaje Pero no es lo
same we are not talking about the
mismo no estamos hablando de lo
same thing okay I think I think we are not
mismo vale creo Creo que no estamos
talking about the same thing but well Hey maybe it is like that I do
hablando de lo mismo pero bueno Oye a lo
n't know the truth but it has
mejor e es así no sé la verdad pero no
shocked me a little having met him and
me ha chocado un poco de haberlo
how we have seen him here and
conocido y de como lo hemos visto aquí y
such and of course knowing that this guy
tal y claro sabiendo que este chico
apart from what he has said about being a
aparte eso que ha dicho de soy
millionaire and such and these things does not give me
millonario y tal y estas cosas no me da
the feeling that it is an outbreak Hey
la sensación de que es un brote Oye
I hope I am
ojalá me
wrong Let's see the subject of
equivoque A ver vamos a ver el tema de
the funa this is not from osu It is that I have no
la funa esta no de osu Es que no tengo
idea what osu is I am going to
ni idea de lo que es osu me voy a
find out here with you Kendo promoter
enterar aquí con ustedes Kendo promotor
of the funa osu osu
de la funa osu
osu accused of  abuse and mistreatment by his
osu acusado de maltrato y abuso por su
ex the end of the vtuber elite roldier
ex el fin de la élite vtuber roldier
linked to
vinculado con
osu well well let's
osu
see let's find out about the
vaya vaya a ver vamos a enterarnos de la
move I mean, I know absolutely nothing
movidad O sea absolutamente no sé nada
eh only that I just saw well
eh solamente que acabo de ver bueno que
yesterday you were bothering me a lot with
ayer me estabais dando mucho [__] con
this
esto
no and that uncle shur has posted a tweet
no y que el tío shur ha puesto un tweet
asking for evidence that's the only thing I've
pidiendo pruebas eso es lo único que he
seen the
visto el
Kendo issue promoter of the funa to
tema Kendo promotor de la funa a
osu accused of mistreatment and abuse by his
osu acusado de maltrato y abusos por su
ex, I mean Kendo is this Uber that has
ex o sea Kendo es este Uber que tiene
742,000 subscribers But osu what is it
742000 suscriptores Pero osu qué es en
specifically what is it a company what
concreto qué es lo que es una empresa de
an agency as if it were a plan
qué una agencia como si fuera un planes
or something like that but exclusively or
o algo así pero exclusivamente o
specialized in
especializados en
vtuber what is it
vtuber qué es lo que es
exactly because he says he was expelled from
exactamente porque dice fue expulsado de
osu an agency okay
osu una agencia vale
perfect and one of those who was
perfecto y uno de los que más estaba
supporting the funa the most I mean after they
apoyando la funa O sea después de que lo
kicked him out not to see click
echen no a ver click
summary
resumen
my dad died of covid and the
mi papá fallece de de covid y yo a la
only person I had at that time was
única persona que tenía en ese entonces
him he was the last person who
era a él él fue la última persona que
knew my dad So I
Que conoció a mi papá Entonces yo me
clung to him Since he has no idea
aferré a él Como no tiene ni idea
always  He says it's just that always whenever
siempre dice es Es que siempre siempre
something happens he always brings up his dad who
que pasa algo siempre saca su papá que
passed away when he was like 15 I don't
falleció cuando él tenía como 15 años no
know why he does it I try not to talk about the fact that
sé por qué lo hace yo intento no hablar
my dad passed away but he always
con que falleció mi papá pero él siempre
does I identified with him and
lo hace me identifiqué con él y
obviously I he gave me love you know he
obviamente yo él me daba amor saben él
gave me love not like the three weeks He
me daba amor no como las tres semanas Él
told me that Hey eh I like you and he
me dijo de que Oye eh Me gustas y se me
declared himself to me and we became a couple Yes yes yes in
declaró y fuimos parejita Sí sí sí en
November it really was a very
noviembre de verdad fue una relación muy
nice relationship the first three months this
bonita los primeros tres meses esta
person was quite is very jealous very
persona era bastante es muy celosa muy
jealous very controlling he was my first
celosa muy controladora él fue mi primer
boyfriend he was my first relationship
novio él fue mi primera relación
So I made a lot of mistakes in the
Entonces yo tuve muchos errores en la
relationship Also a lot of the things
relación También muchas de las cosas que
he told me was that I like
él me decía era de que me gustan las
toxic people I like
personas tóxicas me gustan las chicas
jealous girls and I'm not like that chat he was the one who
celosas y yo no soy así chat él era el
told me I want you to be
que me decía yo quiero que tú seas
toxic and I literally no there was never a
tóxica y yo literal no nunca hubo una
complaint from me and we had a very
queja de mí y tuvimos un problema muy
strong problem eh they were his friends sometimes I
fuerte eh eran sus amigos yo a veces
wanted to do things with my friend and he didn't
quería hacer cosas con mi amigo y él no
want to and it got to such a
quería y llegó a un tanto chat tan
strong chat that he told me either you stop talking
fuerte que él me dijo o dejas de hablar
to that guy or we break up like this he told me
con ese vato o terminamos así me dijo
you are not allowed to talk to this  dude I didn't
tienes prohibido hablar con este vato yo
know I felt like a little cage
no sabía yo me sentía como una jaulita
you know how Oh yeah he's being unfaithful
saben como Ay seje le está siendo infiel
to his dude gey I never ever chat was
a su vato gey yo jamás jamás chat le fui
unfaithful to him but like he said [ __ ] like like
infiel a él pero como él decía cosas
I was with another
pedo de de que como yo estaba con otro
guy gy I can't have friends because you
chico gy no puedo tener amigos porque a
hate me having friends dude I mean
ti te cag que tenga amigos güey O sea de
really There no there things got
verdad Ahí no ahí se puso la cosa
horrible chat there it got ay Okay here there's
horrible chat ahí se puso ahy Okay aquí
a before and after dude and when he
hay un antes y un después güey y cuando
drank a lot chat he's a
tomaba mucho chat es una persona
pretty violent person there were times ch one he would hit me like
bastante violenta habían veces ch una él
this he would say to me you've got me [ __ ] up he would
le pegaba al así me decía ya me tienes
say to me and he would hit me to
hasta la chingada me decía y le pegaba
things like that to me I mean in a few
las a las cosas así al o sea en pocas
words he mistreated me he
palabras me me maltrataba
hit him to the point where he broke his
le pegaba las cosas llegó a romper su
bas Station because pretend that
bas Station porque hagan de cuenta que
one time we're at a party right
una vez estamos en una fiesta verdad
because he only wanted chat me to
porque él solamente quería chat que yo
use skins of mine little ones
usara skins de mía chiquita chiquitas
because that's what was left with my voice dude
porque era lo que quedaba con mi voz gey
one time he got mad at me he hit me so
una vez se enojó conmigo golpeó tan
hard he had he has Well I don't know he
fuerte él tenía él tiene Bueno no sé él
had a case this thing of the dolls that
tenía una cas esto de las muñecas que
inspire like minor characters  of age
inspiran como personajes menores de edad
is something that apparently in ubers it is
es algo que por lo visto en los ubers se
clear but it is because of the style of the
Claro pero es por el estilo de los
drawings I do
dibujos
not know much about the vtuber world more than
no conozco mucho el mundo vtuber más que
what we have talked about some
lo que hemos hablado de algunas
controversies like sui nimu eh hostia
polémicas como lo de sui nimu eh [__]
That nimu comes up it would be the [ __ ] it would be the
Que suba nimu sería la [__] sería la
[ __ ] that nimu came up to talk about this
[__] que subiera nimu a hablar de esto
Well I'm going to find out about La Movida and and we
Bueno me voy a enterar de La Movida y y
call her okay I'm going to find out about La
la llamamos vale me voy a enterar de La
Movida and we contacted her house where her
Movida y la contactamos casa donde sus
walls were like very soft
paredes eran como como muy suavecitas
Then she punched the wall and
Entonces le dio un puñetazo a la pared y
the wall broke dude he made
se rompió la pared güey se le hizo hiz
a hole in it a lot and he said to me Because of you I
un hoyo una badura y me dijo Por tu
get like this because of you I broke
culpa yo me pongo así por tu culpa rompí
the wall that's how it was always like that it was everything it was
la pared así era siempre así era todo
my fault chat everything was my fault everything everything
era mi culpa chat todo era mi culpa todo
that happened was when he started to
todo lo que pasaba era cuando me llegó a
verbally insult me I told him I do
insultar verbalmente Yo le dije a él yo
n't want to go out with you because neither my
no quiero salir contigo porque no ni mi
mom nor my dad nor anyone had
mamá ni mi papá ni nadie me había
spoken to me like you spoke to me
hablado como tú me hablaste el día de
today that day he said to me if you don't come back to the
hoy ese día me dijo si no vuelves a la
call we end things here
llamada terminamos aquí se acaban las
things end and I said yeah yeah  the
cosas y yo le dije sí est al día
next day he sends me a request and says hey I
siguiente me manda request me dice oye
know I was wrong Forgive me but I
Yo sé que estuve mal Perdóname pero me
got really mad because you broke up with me he didn't
dio mucho coraje porque tú me terminaste
apologize cha I got into a really
no se disculpó cha Yo me peleé muy
big fight with my mom because my mom
fuerte con mi mamá porque mi mamá me
told me I don't want you to bring I don't want you to
dijo No quiero que traigas no quiero que
bring him home He told me to
lo traigas a la casa Él me dijo que
go to his hotel to drop off his
fuéramos a a su hotel para dejar sus
things and and well and well I said
cosas y y pues y pues yo dije
Well okay I
Bueno está
went to went we
fui
got to the
fui llegamos al
hotel I sat down on the
hotel me senté yo en la
bed and he closed the
cama y él cerró las
curtains and it looked all
cortinas y se veía todo
dark
oscuro
with a stain right there He just texted me
con manche justo Me acaba de escribir
Right now look he says he replied to a
Ahora mismo mira dice ha contestado a un
tweet in which I said move away his he's
tweet en el que yo puse aparten su está
back okay And I said damn
vuelto vale Y me puse me dice conche
well he said the guy I know what I have to
bien dijo el cabrón sé qu tengo que
do if I want to have 100k but right now
hacer si quiero tener 100k pero ahorita
I feel like being calm and there is
me apetece estar tranquilo y ahí están
the proof totally totally eh
las pruebas totalmente totalmente eh
literal literal
literal
literal I could call him comancha now
literal le podría poner a comancha ahora
and if not you can always see some
y si no siempre se puede ver unos
asses no no no no no no no no
culitos no no no no no no no no
Noa would have been trending that
Noa hubiera sido trending ese
t and and
t y y
and I was really scared chat I was you don't
y yo tenía mucho miedo chat yo tenía no
know how much scared I
saben cuánto miedo
was And then
tenía Y entonces
and he told me that well well I can and I
e me dijo de que pues pues puedo y ya
stayed quiet and and
e me quedé callada
I said here there are
e y y yo dije aquí hay de
two he came from very far away and well the
dos él vino de muy lejos y pues lo
first thing literally Chad is that the
primero literalmente Chad es que lo
first thing he wanted to do when he met me was
primero que quiso hacer al conocerme fue
that you know I mean it wasn't like I told him
eso saben o sea no fue de que yo le dije
let's go to the plaza no I mean really
vamos a la plaza no O sea de verdad
then I
entonces yo
said well well yes Then
dije pues pues sí
since he was already
Entonces ya de que de que ya este
and I went to bed and well well you know
e me acosté y pues pues ya saben
no after that he told me I was I
no después de eso él me dijo yo estaba
was very bad chat I was I started
yo estaba muy mal chat Yo estaba me puse
to cry I was very very bad really
a llorar estaba muy muy mal de verdad
too
demasiado
bad and he told me and he
mal y él me
told me and I
dijo y él me
turned to look at me and he said it
dijo y volti a ver y me dijo
seems it seems like I just raped you like
e parece parece que te acabo de violar
that he
así me
told me and I I stayed
dijo y yo me yo me quedé
and and I said that well it's that I didn't want to
y y dije de que pues es que yo no quería
or I mean I because chat when we were when we
o sea yo lo porque chat cuando
were before we saw each other I
estábamos antes de que nos viéramos yo
told him many times that I didn't
le dije muchas veces a él que yo no
want to do anything with him that when we
quería hacer nada con él que cuando nos
saw each other I didn't want to do anything with him
viéramos yo no quería hacer nada con él
because chat I hadn't even
porque chat yo ni siquiera un beso había
given a kiss I hadn't even given a kiss in my life
dado yo ni un beso había dado en mi vida
dude Then I told him I don't want to
güey Entonces yo le dije yo no quiero
do anything with you I told him But  he didn't
hacer nada contigo le dije Pero a él le
care and when we were in the room
valió y cuando estábamos en el cuarto
obviously I was so
pues obviamente ch yo estaba tan
manipulated dude well it was something
manipulada güey pues fue fue algo
horrible dude it was me and I told him and
horrible güey fue yo le Y yo le dije Y
I told him that I didn't want to do
yo le dije a él que yo no quería hacer
anything because for me my concept of
nada porque para mí mi concepto de de
having a relationship with someone relationships
tener relación con alguien relaciones
with someone is for me that's what it was like being
con alguien es para mí así era estar
married being together and when we were
casados estar juntos y ya cuando éramos
married then having the honeymoon
casados pues ahí tener la luna de miel
I told him that's why I don't want to do
yo le dije por eso yo no quiero hacer
anything with you because I don't want my
nada contigo porque yo no quiero que mi
first time to be with someone that I do
primera vez sea con alguien a quien yo
n't want you know or rather who I'm not going to
no quiero saben o sea quien yo no me voy
marry I told him like that and he didn't care she
a casar yo le dije así a él y a él le
's a minor no I understand that she's
valió es una menor no yo entiendo que es
a minor no because she's talking about her
una menor no porque está hablando de su
first
primera
time I tried to ignore that and I had a
vez traté de ignorar eso y y me la pasé
great time chat I had a great time the
muy bien chat Yo me la pasé muy bien la
truth is I took him everywhere chat
verdad lo llevé a todos lados chat a
all over Mexico I took him to Sochimilco I
todo México lo llevé a sochimilco lo
took him everywhere Oh another thing he
llevé a a todos lados Ah otra cosa él me
forced me to take and he forced me to take
obligó a tomarme y me obligó a tomarme
the pill that hormonal pill I don't know
la pastilla esa pastilla hormonal no sé
what it's called the one with hormones and I
cómo se llame la que tiene hormonas y yo
didn't I didn't want to because  in the [ __ ]
no yo no quería porque en el [__]
instructions dude in the [ __ ] instructions it
instructivo gey en el [__] instructivo
says that many bad consequences dude he
dice que muchas consecuencias malas güey
told me a week after I
me dijo una semana después de que yo
had intimacy with him he said We have to
tuve intimidad con él me dijo Tenemos
talk the truth is that we can't
que hablar la verdad es que ya no ya no
be together anymore He told me we can't
podemos estar juntos me dijo ya no
be together anymore I don't
podemos estar juntos
want anything with you anymore And obviously
no quiero nada contigo ya Y obviamente
I begged him and I said Hey
yo le rogué y le dije Oye
but but it's that I told you that
pero pero es que yo te dije a ti que que
I didn't want to do anything Unless I
yo no quería hacer nada A menos que
had someone
tuviera alguien
eh with like someone to marry me
eh con o sea con quién casarme
he was 19 and she was 18 Yeah he said No
yo él tenía 19 y ella 18 Ajá me dijo No
well and then he said It's that I don't even
pues y luego me dijo Es que ni siquiera
know why I
yo sé por qué lo
did it gy how that hurt me dude
hice gy cómo me dolió eso chado De
Really He told me I mean he told me that he did
verdad Él me dijo o sea de que me dijo
n't want me to bother him that he
de que no quería que lo molestara que él
was already doing his thing and that and and
ya estaba haciendo su sus cosas y que y
that no I didn't have any knowledge
y que no no tenía nada de conocimiento
you know I had vomited blood came out of my
sabes tenía vomité me salió sangre de la
nose I
nariz me
fainted I said dude I feel really bad and I took I
desmayé dije güey Yo estoy muy mal y me
took two
hice me hice me hice dos pruebas de
pregnancy tests and they came out positive
embarazo y y salieron salieron positivas
when he was intimate with me He told me
cuando tuvo intimidad conmigo Él me dijo
don't tell anyone that we did anything He
no le digas a nadie que hicimos nada Él
said No don't tell your mom
me dijo No no se lo comentes a tu mamá
Then ch I didn't have anyone I didn't
Entonces ch yo no tenía nadie no se lo
tell your mom she noticed for God's sake
comenté a tu mamá le dio nota por Dios
nobody knew I was alone she said jeje
nadie sabía estaba sola me dijo seje por
please already says Ofelia 10 members just
favor ya é dice Ofelia 10 miembros acaba
gave a kiss Ofelia a huge kiss
de regalar un beso Ofelia un beso enorme
Thank you so much you're a stalker if you're
Muchísimas gracias eres una acosadora di
serious are you serious That after
es en serio es en serio Eso después de
that I said You know that already I mean I've already gotten
eso dije Sabes que ya O sea ya me humé
really angry all December I was
mucho gey todo diciembre le estuve
telling him that we should talk that please
diciendo que habláramos que por favor
think things through he washed his hands and
pensara las cosas él se lavó las manos y
said I'm not going to say anything people will
dijo yo no voy a decir nada la gente se
realize on their own that
dará cuenta por sí sola que ya no
we're not together anymore and what do you think happened
estamos juntos y qué creen que pasó
to me all the people who do you think
conmigo toda la gente a quién creen que
came to throw [ __ ] at the one who had the
le vino a echar caca al que tenía la
huge community or the one with the
comunidad gigante o a la que tenía la
smallest community Well I didn't say
comunidad más pequeña Pues a mí no dije
anything I'm not I'm not a minor I
nada no soy no soy menor de edad Yo lo
met him when I was a minor I
conocí a él siendo menor de edad yo
was 17 years old and he was 18 when I
tenía 17 años y él tenía 18 cuando yo lo
met him but we were
conocí pero nosotros nos llevamos
only a year apart at that time when
solamente un año en ese entonces cuando
what I told you happened I was 18 and he
pasó lo que les conté yo tenía 18 y él
was 19 no it wasn't  we were
tenía 19 no no fue éramos mayores de
both of legal age he notices people who
edad los dos él se fija en en personas
have a squeaky voice he likes it
que tiene la voz chillona a él le gusta
like girls ch you know what he told me to
así como niñas ch sabes qué me decía que
say bro dude that's what he told me tell me
dijera hermanito güey así me decía dime
bro tell me bro And I what what I
hermanito dime hermanito Y yo qué qué
saw and things like that or and I with skin one of
vi y cosas así o y yo con skin una de
a girl gey I mean me Us little skins
una niña gey o sea yo Us skin chiquitas
Oh no God everything I did ch was
Ay no Dios todo lo que yo hacía ch era
heado I started hanging out I tried to
heado yo me empecé a juntar intenté
put things aside with him gey and I
dejar de lado las cosas con él gey y me
started hanging out with streamers a little
empecé a juntar con streamers un poco
older than him kiss gorgeous they
más grandes que beso guapísimo me
started putting me all over Oh here comes the
empezaron a poner todos Ay ya va la
hangup he says that I didn't support him that I don't
colgada él dice que yo no lo apoyaba que
know what but really you guys
no sé qué pero de verdad ustedes no
have no idea of everything I
tienen una idea de todo lo
tried to do to help him I've been
que intenté hacer para ayudarlo he
living where people don't want to
estado viviendo donde la gente no quiere
hang out with me because I'm his
juntarse conmigo porque soy su
ex because I was supposedly the toxic one the bad one
ex porque yo según era la tóxica la mala
gey I'm really fed up with him he talked about me
gey de verdad estoy harta él habló de mí
with the person I was
con la persona con la que yo estaba
dating gey two years have passed since we started together
quedando gey pasó dos años de lo nuestro
dude you have to keep getting into
güey tienes que seguir entr metiéndome
my things after 2  years you have to
en mis cosas después de 2 años tienes
keep talking bad about me after
que seguir hablando mal de mí después de
so long
tanto tiempo
never contain anything of everything that
jamás conten nada de todo lo que
happened okay here if I have not understood wrong the
pasó vale aquí si no he entendido mal la
girl is
chica está
recounting abuse I do not understand what she is
contando un abuso no entiendo que está
recounting an abuse that she is
contando un abuso que está
recounting well that she had a boyfriend a
relatando pues que tenía un novio un
boy that she met not with whom she
chico al que conoció no con el que
lost her virginity also
pierde la virginidad además
eh And
eh Y
what and that the boy treated her very
que y que el chico la trataba muy
badly but I understand that what you are
mal pero entiendo que lo que estás
recounting is abuse is
relatando es un abuso
not like that or is not like that guys before
no es así o no es así chavales antes de
moving on to the next
pasar al siguiente
point I understand that the boy takes
punto entiendo que el chico la se
advantage of her, he abuses her No her what she
aprovecha de ella la la busa No ella lo
feels at
que se siente por lo
least what she perceives that she has been abused
menos lo que percibe que la han abusado
no While she was like
no Mientras que ella estaba como
unconscious or is it the
inconsciente o es la
moved relationship without consent but
movida relación sin consentimiento pero
of course what I have not what I have not
claro lo que no he lo que no he
realized is if she was unconscious or
percatado yo es si estaba inconsciente o
how she accuses him of mistreatment relationship
cómo lo acusa de malos tratos relación
with her without consent and of
con ella sin consentimiento y de
forcing her to take the pill the
obligarla a tomar la pastilla el día
after and still she got
después e igualmente se quedó
pregnant but she was not
embarazada pero no estaba
unconscious that is what I am telling you I mean what are we
inconsciente por eso es lo que te digo o
talking about here without
sea de qué hablamos aquí sin
consent yes yes at no time
consentimiento si si en ningún momento
was she unconscious she was
estaba inconsciente
not Ah that it is abuse because she
no estaba Ah que que es un abuso porque
was manipulated Ah but that is not  I do
estaba manipulada Ah pero eso no s yo si
count as abuse, eh, I mean, we're
cuenta como abuso eh o sea estamos
talking about him and 19, she's
hablando de él con 19 ella
18 m. I don't, I don't know if that counts as
18 m Yo no no sé si eso cuenta como
abuse. So, you being very much in love, something
abuso O sea que tú estés muy enamorada
else, that the guy is an [ __ ] and
otra cosa que el chico sea un cabrón y
first goes along with it to sleep
primero te siga el rollo para acostarse
with you, then he says no, whoever swims
contigo luego te diga que no quien nada
with you is worth it, but of course that as abuse,
contigo vale pero claro eso como abuso
as a relationship without consent, doesn't
como relación sin consentimiento no
count. Let's keep reading to see if
cuenta vamos a seguir leyendo a ver si
we find out more about the story,
nos enteramos más de la historia
okay? Kendo announced that he will respond
vale Kendo anunció que responderá en
live in a while, if it's soon, I attacked him, let's
directo en un rato si es pronto lo agre
see. V, let's see. Oh, so we're
a ver V vamos a ver Ah o sea que estamos
following this thing, it's happening right
siguiendo est esta movida está pasando
now, she
ahora
felt manipulated into doing it.
mismo se sintió manipulada para hacerlo
Of course, but that doesn't quantify as abuse,
Claro pero eso como abuso no no
eh, that's abuse. It would only be
eh que eso como abuso Ya solo
missing that for you, nothing else.
faltaría que eso ya para vm no otra cosa
That the guy is an [ __ ], that the guy
Que que el tío sea un cabrón que el tío
is a manipulator is
sea un manipulador
worth a thousand things, but man, it doesn't count
vale mil cosas pero hombre no cuenta
as abuse. I'm aware of the
como abuso estoy al tanto de la
situation, more at night I'll do a live
situación más a la noche haré directo
talking about everything, I'll announce here when it
hablando de todo avisaré por aquí cuando
starts so you can be attentive.
prende para que estén atentos
Look at the cat, the cat is very involved
Mira el gato el gato está metid issimo
in this funa, eh,
en esta funa eh
geshe just said publicly that
geshe acaba de decir públicamente que
Kendo  sexually abused her
Kendo abusó sexualmente de ella
rape Well he tells us that after
violación Pues nos relata que después de
a sexual encounter he told her it seems like I just
un encuentro sexual él le dijo parece
raped you but it seems like I
que te acabo de violar pero parece que
just raped you it
te acabo de violar
sounds to me like a phrase that he would
me suena a mí a una frase que él le
say to her because since it was her
diría a ella porque ella al ser su
first time she wouldn't
primera vez pues no
be the most imaginative in
sería la más imaginativa en la
bed and she would be throwing in his face
cama y le estaría como echando en cara
that she hadn't done anything, that she hadn't
que ella no habría hecho nada que no se
moved or something like that, I imagine that's where
ha movido o algo así yo me imagino que
the shots go
van por ahí los tiros
eh I imagine that they go for the shots it
eh yo me imagino que van por los tiros
is abuse there is no doubt and Hi Javi Yes
es abuso no ha duda y Hola Javi Sí es
this is not
que esto no es
abuse or
abuso
your agency let's see what
osu agencia vamos a ver que tiene que
this has to do with the cancellation of this company
ver esto con la cancelación a la empresa
that is being talked about not an
esta que de lo que se está hablando no
agency Uber controlled according to the
agencia Uber controlada según la
vanguard by
vanguardia por
misra drat And
misra drat Y
roldier
roldier
how
cómo
How do you know who roldier is no that he
Cómo sabéis Quién es roldier no que
has a [ __ ] gameover here
tiene un gameover aquí de la [__] [__]
no but I knew that he was very good friends with
no pero yo sabía que él era muy amigo de
misra yes always for
misra eso sí de siempre de hace
many years but Drake Coat they have
muchísimos años pero Drake Coat tienen
a
una
company they have a company let's see I know
empresa tienen una empresa a ver yo sé
that
que
Drake with the issue of vtuber no  and uploads
Drake con el tema de de vtuber no y sube
a lot of content on Twitter from vtuber and I
mucho contenido en Twitter de vtuber y
think he was like a gossip youtuber
creo que era como un youtuber de salseo
but from
pero de de
vtubers
vtubers
LOL according to the vanguard okay And what's
LOL según la vanguardia vale Y qué es lo
going on in the company apparently
que pasa en la empresa al parecer
some avatars of the ub tubers that
algunos avatares de las ub tubers que se
retired are property of osu
retiraron son propiedad de osu por lo
so they couldn't use them
que no podrían utilizarlos
anymore let's see let's
más a ver vamos a
see it and rabit who would be part of w
verlo y rabit quién formaría parte de w
would make the following statements
realizaría las siguientes declaraciones
right now it is being negotiated
ahora mismo se está negociando por
privately with the girls through their
privado con las chicas por sus
respective emails these responses take
respectivos correos estas respuestas
time since they require an
tienen su tardanza ya que requieren un
analysis of all the contexts many
análisis de todos los contextos muchas
demand responses in
exigen respuestas en tiempos
extremely short times but in these
extremadamente cortos pero en estas
circumstances they are simply not
circunstancias Simplemente no son
possible when they chose
posibles cuando eligieron una
formal communication by email through
comunicación formal por correo a través
legal advisors unilaterally
de asesores legales de manera unilateral
and on the part of many without asking for another means
y por parte de muchas sin pedir otra vía
of contact unfortunately for my
de contacto desafortunadamente por mi
part I can't do much more since I don't
parte no puedo hacer mucho más ya que no
have them at the end of the act that she started
tengo los al final del acto que se puso
to cry because she only wanted to have
a llorar porque ella solo quería tener
relations with the person she
relaciones con la persona con la que
was married to and her first time she
estuviera casada y su primera vez la
wanted to have it on her honeymoon from there
quería tener en la luna de miel de ahí
when he saw her crying he told her that it seemed
al el verla llorando le dijo que parecía
that he had raped her
que la había violado
Oh by the reaction she was having
Ah por la reacción que estaba teniendo
not the
no la
situation anymore  but let's see,
situación ya pero vamos a ver es que a
the phrase can mean whatever it
la frase puede significar lo que
means, okay, I'm watching the story.
signifique vale estoy viendo la historia
Eh. This is a 21-minute video that
Eh Esto es un vídeo de 21 minutos que
says luar, which is a
dice luar que es un
summary, the mother who
resumen la madre que me
gave birth to me, a video with the whole context of the
parió vídeo con todo el contexto de la
funa. Well, come on, let's watch it.
funa bueno venga vamos a verlo la La
The thing is that you have to get a good understanding of things, eh. To talk about this because we're
la cosa eh Para hablar de esto porque
talking about serious issues and accusations.
estamos hablando de temas y acusaciones
Trianero, a handsome kiss. Let's see.
serias trianero un beso guapo a ver
Eh, what the girl has reported is not
eh lo que la chica ha relatado no es un
abuse, and then you. Ah, it's not that she was
abuso que luego tú Ah no es que estaba
manipulated, man. Of course, now
manipulada hombre claro ahora entonces
based on that, you go around accusing
en base a eso ya pues tú vas acusando de
whoever you want of being an abuser, okay,
abusadora quien te de a ti la gana vale
obviously, a guy who wants to
evidentemente una un chico que se quiere
sleep with you, will eat you out, and will
acostar contigo te a comer y te va a
give you his ear.
regalar la oreja
Ah, he took advantage of my innocence,
Ah es que se aprovechado de mi inocencia
man. Okay, but let's
hombre ya pero a
see, I don't understand that as abuse, that
ver yo no entiendo eso como un abuso que
a manipulator takes advantage of you, a bastard,
se aproveche un manipulador un cabrón
but abuse. That's not abuse, it's taking
pero un abuso No es eso un abuso es que
advantage of a person who is not
se aprovechen de una persona que no está
in full possession of their faculties to give
en sus plenas facultades para dar
consent or that there is force, not an
consentimiento o que haya una fuerza no
obligation by force, what is that?  it would already
una obligación por la fuerza que es eso
be a violation at least here
ya sería una violación por lo menos aquí
in Spain corresponding knowledge
en España conocimientos correspondientes
to carry out the situation by
para llevar a cabo la situación por mí
myself the only thing I can promise you at the
mismo lo único que les puedo prometer de
moment is that this will not become
momento Es que esto no se convertirá en
a W of Face to the filtration of the
un W de Cara a la filtración de los
girls' personal data it was never
datos personales de las chicas nunca fue
our intention to reach a point of
nuestra intención llegar a un punto de
that nature I can not comment much more
esa índole no puedo comentar mucho más
since that would imply breaking different
ya que eso implicaría romper diferentes
confidentiality documents to which
documentos de confidencialidad al cual
at least I am respecting on the
por lo menos yo sí estoy respetando por
other hand gbel would publish screenshots of
otro lado gbel publicaría capturas de
tweets from a person who apparently
tweets de una persona que al parecer
would work with osu who would expose them by
trabajaría con osu quién los expondría
mentioning this in it You could see
mencionando esto en ella Se podrían ver
tweets that would say osu and drakeout which
tweets que pondrían osu y drakeout qué
minutes later Juri doog would delete them
minutos después Juri doog los borraría
however hours after
sin embargo horas después de publicado
those tweets were published they would say voos work
esos tweets se pondrían voos trabaj
let's read it these are the
vamos a leerlo estos son los trapos más
dirtiest laundry of osu one of its
sucios de osu a uno de sus creadores de
content creators was silenced for talking about
contenido lo silenciaron por hablar de
the bad things of the platform and There are
las cosas malas de la plataforma y Hay
many worse things yet they cannot be
muchísimas cosas peores aún no se pueden
said I will keep you informed when
decir los mantendré informados cuando
I asked things they did not answer me they never
preguntaba cosas no me respondían jamás
helped me with the content and I
me ayudaron con el contenido y
practically had to figure it out myself
prácticamente tenía que ingeniármelas yo
the editing issue didn't last long in
en el tema de edición no duró nada en
the live streams I did and videos I sent
los directos que hice y vídeos que mandé
Only two came out they always saw us
Solo dos salieron siempre nos vieron
as replaceable people Drake is an
como gente reemplazable Drake es un caso
incredible case while I was asking
increíble mientras yo estaba preguntando
things for the content like doing
cosas para el contenido como hacer las
things and Editors issues he didn't
cosas y temas de los Editores él no me
answer me and only spoke to it by
respondía y solo hablaba con eto
displacing him the only time I had
desplazándolo la única vez que tuve
contact with him was to give him the idea
contacto con él fue para darle la idea
of reviving hiru
de revivir a hiru
Dodge for April Fools' Day
Dodge por el día de los inocentes a
sometimes he didn't answer and when he did answer me he did
veces no respondía y cuando me respondía
n't say anything Only that we were going to
no me decía nada Solo que sí lo íbamos a
do it just for the day before
hacer recién para el día anterior a día
today the inente gave me the idea of what to
de hoy los inente me dio la idea de qué
do and I couldn't prepare
hacer y no pude preparar
anything they have no coordination and
nada no tienen nada de coordinación y
the ideas that are had must always be
siempre las ideas que se tienen deben
passed on to the higher ups let's
pasarse a los altos mandos a ver lo que
see what I'm understanding of this funa in this thread this complaint let's call it a complaint because here at the moment I don't see funa either I'm also telling you, I mean here it's basically a complaint I'm simply telling them to support the girls in
chicas en
all okay
todos vale
There the number of girls is coming down on them
Ahí se le están viniendo encima las
no let's see but What is the accusation here
no a ver pero Cuál es la acusación aquí
what  they are complaining that it is
lo que se están quejando es de que sea
a bad Network, let's go here what they
una mala Network vamos aquí de lo que se
are complaining about what all the
está quejando de lo que hacen todas las
Networks do from another account asking for forgiveness I
Network de otra cuenta pidiendo perdón
apologize to all the
pido disculpas a todos los
members of obos especially
pertenecientes de obos sobre todo
@ the whole context but labor abuses
@ todo el contexto pero abusos laborales
and account theft a kiss Michel who was
y robo de cuentas un beso Michel que fue
a good friend of mine and I did not even consult
un buen amigo mío y ni siquiera consulté
things with him I was overcome by the impulsiveness
las cosas con él me ganó la impulsividad
of the moment and I did not manage it well I was
del momento y no lo gestion bien fui
totally irresponsible and I apologize a thousand
totalmente irresponsable y pido mil
times for what happened I deleted everything
disculpas por lo sucedido eliminé todo
regarding the subject of truth I am sorry
con respecto al tema de verdad perdón
on the other hand after this situation with
por otro lado tras esta situación con
osu labit ber Kendo would speak out about it
osu labit ber Kendo se pronunciaría al
mentioning that they wanted to
respecto mencionando que la querían
defame her I am glad that my friends
difamar Me da gusto que mis amigas por
are finally rising up in voice against
fin se están levantando en voz en contra
all the mistreatment that osu does where
de todos los maltratos que hac osu donde
even I myself had very bad
incluso yo mismo tuve muy malas
experiences because they wanted to defame me
experiencias porque me querían difamar
girls you are not alone you have my full
chicas no están solas tienen todo mi
support in this cause anything you
apoyo en esta causa cualquier cosa que
need Here I am, they are done with that
necesiten Aquí estoy ya se Les acabo esa
Blacklist obu on the other hand according to K
Lista negra obu por otro lado según K
Channel would comment that this new bber
Channel comentaría que este nuevo bber
announced by osu would be drakeout
anunciado por osu sería drakeout
then that bber would expose  drakeout
seguidamente ese bber expondría drakeout
as follows and I would comment on this
de la siguiente manera y comentaría esto
about a Blacklist that the
de una Lista negra que tendría la
agency would have. I don't understand why they gave
agencia yo no entiendo por le dieron a
dro so much power within the community
dro Tanto poder dentro de la comunidad
when we could always make content
cuando siempre pudimos hacer contenido
whenever and with whoever the [ __ ] we wanted.
como cuando y con quien chucha nos diera
In 2021, he suggested I go to
la gana a mí en el 2021 me sugirió ir a
the English community after my funa. He
la comunidad inglesa tras mi funa Lo
did the same thing to then accuse him of
mismo hizo con para luego acusarlo de
running away and funar some time after I had
huir y funar tiempo después de yo haber
accepted that horrible advice, I would not have been
aceptado ese horrible consejo no podría
able to continue making
haber sido capaz de seguir haciendo
content Dr. we have seen
contenido Dr hemos hemos visto aquí
some things here, right? A little on some
alguna cosilla verdad un po en algunas
occasions, right? He claimed the likes he
ocasiones verdad reclamaba los likes que
gave and whenever he could, he wanted to contribute
daba y siempre que podía quería aportar
to further crushing my reputation. Tubers
a aplastar aún más mi reputación tubers
and content creators, stop
y creadores de contenido dejen de
depending on other people to
depender de otras personas para
build communities, believe in your
construir comunidades crean en sus
talents and entertainment capacity.
talentos Y capacidad de entretenimiento
The monopoly exists because you
el monopolio existe porque ustedes lo
allow it, do what you want. With
permiten hagan lo que quieran Con
whoever you want, that's why I never tire
quienes quieran por eso nunca me canso
of saying that even if an agency
de decir que aunque una agencia te
gives you numbers and it seems like the easiest path
regale números y parece el camino más
to success and fame, there is nothing
fácil para éxito y la fama no hay nada
like the peace of mind of working for what's
como la tranquilidad de chambear por lo
yours and that no one can ever
tuyo y que nadie nunca te lo pueda
take it away from you. Up with the independent tubers
quitar arriba las tubers independientes
tinas, the blacklist is real and it works
tinas lo de la lista negra es real y va
beyond any funa and so they
más allá de cualquier funa y así
literally banned coaps if they closed
literalmente prohibían coaps si cerraban
doors and someone was a friend of mine and
puertas y alguien era amigo mío y
whenever someone invited me to something they
siempre que alguien me invitaba a algo
always pushed me aside so it wouldn't
siempre me hac a un lado para que no
affect their work. to this
afectara su trabajo a este tweet de la
blacklist tweet I would give some context in
lista negra daría un poco de contexto en
a response mentioning this from a
una respuesta mencionando esto de una
bber called merch who would later be
bber llamada merch quien Más adelante se
revealed to be jeo one of the
revelaría que fue jeo una de las
founders of osu Hey but mer la
fundadoras de osu Oigan pero mer la
exeto had already said about the
exeto ya había dicho sobre lo del
workplace abuse and many bosu girls
maltrato laboral y muchas chicas de bosu
went after her and dismissed her
se le fueron encima y desestimaron sus
demands a year later time proves her
demandas un año después el tiempo le da
right we have short memories
la razón tenemos memoria corta
basically this drot is in charge of making
básicamente esto drot se encarga de
talents go viral by smoking
viralizar talentos a base de fumar a
others when he made nori funa viral to nimu
otros cuando viralizó a nori funa a nimu
when he made nimu viral he was hitting on other
cuando viraliza a nimu le tiraba a otros
tubers and when he was in charge of bosu he would
tubers y cuando estuvo a cargo de bosu
n't stop sharing info he had on
no paraba de compartir info que tenía de
nimu when he was his manager now that it is
nimu cuando era su manager ahora que se
known that rlock was still working within
sabe que rlock seguía trabajando dentro
osu it makes much more sense that riglo
de osu tiene mucho más sentido que riglo
too riglo is also involved in
también riglo también está metido en
this
esto
riglo is also involved in
riglo también está metido en esta
this riglo thing they funneled him they didn't we were seeing here like they funneled him no and and he was like missing and and recently it's not that there is Well yes you could say that he has appeared no I mean a video was recommended to me and it was a new channel in which riglo continued to be carried out I
nuevo en el que segía llevándose riglo
think but I think it was not the same channel
creo pero creo que no era el mismo canal
as always and suddenly it had many
de siempre y de repente tenía muchas
visits
visitas
that many media outlets and
que muchos medios de difusión y canales
criticism channels did not do about it not even
de críticas no hicieran al respecto ni
a quarter of the videos that were
la cuarta parte de los videos que me
dedicated to me they did not want to look bad or
dedicaron a mí no querían quedar mal ni
lose contacts of the company after this
perder contactos de la empresa tras este
point I have to tell you that after this
punto he de contarte que tras este
general pronouncement
pronunciamiento general se empezarían a
some beers would begin to be recognized it is true that
reconocer algunas beers es verdad como
the funa of riglo went a little too far
que se pasó un poco de la funa de riglo
true that they once worked with oso
verdad que alguna vez trabajaron con oso
who had to change their name and
quienes tuvieron que cambiar de nombre y
Avatar apparently for legal reasons
de Avatar al parecer por temas legales
since according to comments the avatars and
ya que según comentan los avatares y
names belonged to this agency
nombres pertenecían a esta agencia
also a youtuber named kali would
Asimismo una youtuber llamada kali
also expose drakeout mentioning
también expondría a drakeout mencionando
that he manipulated her for this that I
que la manipulaba por esto que
would comment I was not wrong to separate myself
comentaría yo no estaba mal al separarme
from that if someone to talk to I am
de que si alguien con quien hablar estoy
here tired of that  They treat us
acá cansada de que a nosotras nos traten
like crazy when the problem was always with
de locas cuando el problema siempre lo
those above me the same thing happened to me
tuvieron los de arriba me pasó lo mismo
when I fought with Sui it was the
cuando me peleé con sui fue culpa del
boy's fault that he came to tell me
muchacho que viniera a decirme
wrong information and above all put me
información errada y sobre todo ponerme
against my friend it is the manipulation
en contra de mi amiga es la manipulación
that he has always carried out and the only
que siempre ha llevado él y la única
way I could understand it was
forma en la que pude entenderlo fue
several years later he acted like a
varios años después se hacía el
poor thing when it was always the
pobrecito cuando siempre fue lo
opposite he always saw for himself
contrario siempre vio por sí mismo
also a vituber who
también una vituber que trabajó
previously worked there would be gif who would
anteriormente allí sería gif quien se
express herself in the following way after
expresaría de la siguiente manera tras
a person recognizes that she
una persona reconocer que ella
was previously Pandora Likewise
anteriormente fue Pandora Asimismo Akira
Virtual Akira would mention this about the said
virtual mencionaría esto sobre la dicha
Blacklist for personal reasons
Lista negra por motivos personales
because getting tired of working
porque cansarse de trabajar
completely alone with the editor being
completamente sola con el editor ser
treated like stupid constantly
tratada como estúpida constantemente
forcing you to believe that you have to compete
obligarte a a creer que hay que competir
instead of working together and also
en vez de trabajar juntas y además
making you work with a guy founded
hacerte trabajar con un sujeto funado
by p of serer ofilia are my problems
por p de serer ofilia son problemas míos
the blacklist is real I have had to
lo de la lista negra es real me ha
see how the doors were closed
tocado ver cómo le cerraban las puertas
to my girls just because in high
a mis niñas solo porque en los altos
command Back then they fell badly they
mandos En ese entonces se caían pésimo
formed rivalries where in reality they
formaron rivalidades donde en realidad
never existed later on a creator
nunca hubieron más adelante una creadora
called NF youtuber  I would mention that she
llamada NF youtuber mencionaría que ella
would be one of the people who would be on
sería una de las personas que estaría en
said blacklist and that it entailed this
dicha Lista negra y que conllevaba ello
as many know or maybe but let's see it
como muchos saben o tal vez pero a ver
seems like [ __ ] to me from funa no let's
me parece una gilipollez de funa no a
see sirita the worst of osu and
ver sirita se revela lo peor de osu y
riglock is revealed let's see what the worst is let's see
riglock a ver cuál es lo peor a ver
tell me the worst because if not it's that I
cuéntame lo peor porque si no es que
'm boring osu not only exploits
estoy aburriendo osu no solo explota a
its workers for years they have also
sus trabajadoras desde hace años también
worked with rigl for years that I grume
trabajan hace años con rigl que me grume
ah This is the girl well or not or is it another one she
ah Esta es la chica bueno o no o es otra
sexually abused me and manipulated me to
abusó sexualmente y me manipuló para
live with him in a relationship she is the girl
vivir con él en una relación es la chica
With only 15 years old This is the girl who
Con solo 15 años Esta es la chica que le
funo there is evidence but they did not ignore it and
funo hay pruebas pero no lo ignoraron y
continued working with
siguieron trabajando con
him
él
roldier worked with
roldier trabajaba con
riglo having gone through
riglo habiendo pasado
this a lot of strength to all the girls who
esto mucha fuerza a todas las chicas que
are fighting against how much the
están luchando contra lo mucho que la
company exploited them it is horrible that they
empresa las explotó es horrible que
have endured this for so long but it does
hayan aguantado tanto tiempo esto pero
sound to me that
si me suena que
riglo could not see roldier and roldier could not see
riglo a roldier no lo podía ver y
rl either no it's that I do not
roldier a rl tampoco no es que no
understand it's as if they had a
entiendo es como si si tuvieran una
double
doble
life in which they have a company But
vida en la que tienen una empresa Pero
eh publicly even privately it's
eh públicamente incluso privadamente es
as if no no no that double
como si no no no existiera esa doble
life didn't exist That second life not in which they
vida Esa segunda vida no de en la que
run a company
llevan una empresa
together yes the funa of riglo we think we
juntos sí la funa de riglo nosotros creo
watched it here live what
que la miramos aquí en directo lo que
happens is that it was like a lot of that
pasa es que como que se pasó mucho de
no no it went
eso no no se hizo
viral
viral
And yes yes there was evidence the truth is I don't know
Y sí si había pruebas la verdad no sé
how old rilo is and I don't know the truth
qué edad tiene rilo y no lo sé la verdad
but it's important if the girl is 15
pero es importante si la chica tiene 15
yes it's not the age of consent
sí que no es la edad de consentimiento
yet but it depends on the age of
todavía pero depende de la edad que
the others it depends on the age if it's
tengan los otros dependen de la edad si
not many years of difference it depends
no son muchos años de diferencia depende
on the sexual maturity of the girl it's like
de la madurez sexual de la chica es como
on a legal level it would be a little subjective
a nivel legal sería un poco subjetivo
let's say okay man let's see if you're 30
digamos vale hombre a ver si tienes 30
years old he's hooking up with a 15 year old
años te está liando con una de 15
obviously it's a crime but if
evidentemente si es delito pero si
you're 15 years old and you're hooking up
tienes 15 años y te estás liando A lo
Maybe I mean if you're 18
mejor O sea si tienes 18
19 20 it depends okay And you're hooking up with
19 20 depende vale Y te estás liando con
someone 15 or 15 to 16 it
alguien de 15 o 15 para 16 es que
depends it's very subjective each case okay it
depende es muy subjetivo cada caso vale
depends on the sexual age of the two of you
depende de la edad sexual de los dos de
sexual maturity Better said but let's see  that they
la madurez sexual Mejor dicho pero a ver
were together that there was a threesome there
que estaban junto que había un trío ahí
the truth was proven things as they are That's how it is
se se probó la verdad las cosas como son
Paule is also involved in the funa
paule también está metido en la funa
paau what are you
paau qu me estás
containing me that you are
container que me estás
containing me mistreatment in the agency let's
container malos tratos en la agencia a
see what kind of
ver cuáles son los malos
mistreatment my ex-boss supported the lies and
tratos mi exjefe apoyaba las mentiras y
defamation that they made against me
difamaciones que hacían contra mí
after leaving his workplace
después de salir de su lugar de trabajo
with all the employees but let's see
con todas las empleadas pero verl es
what kind of
cuál es el
mistreatment is let's see personally with the time we've
maltrato a ver personalmente con el rato
been in funa I have to tell you that I
que llevamos de funa tengo que deciros
'm seeing it a little stupid eh
que la estoy viendo un poco chorra eh la
I'm seeing it a little stupid I don't know if it's
estoy viendo un poco chorra no sé si me
going to surprise me and suddenly
va a sorprender y de repente va a salir
something incredible is going to come out but for
algo increíble pero de momento hasta
now what we're seeing
ahora lo que estamos viendo Me está
seems a little
pareciendo un poquillo
stupid to me Javi Hello Can I ask you a
chorra Javi Hola Te puedo hacer una
question what happened with laser he's
pregunta qué pasó con láser está
disappeared do you know
desaparecido sabes
something ask about that to
algo a pregunta por
me Of course because as I have a
ese a mí Claro porque como tengo un
contact with him well I have no idea let's go
contacto con él pues ni idea vamos
first news that I have that I know
primera noticia que tengo yo que sé
Eh I have no idea the
Eh no tengo ni idea la
truth It seems a little stupid to me
verdad Me está pareciendo un poco chorra
eh I mean I don't know if something strong is going to come out now
eh o sea no sé si va a salir ahora algo
this is
fuerte esto es
all the mistreatment What
todo los malos tratos Cuáles
are they Thank you for  come on I love you all
son Gracias por pasarse Los quiero
so much let's see let's listen to this by
mucho a ver vamos a escuchar esto por
audio let's see come on It
audio a ver venga
seems a little stupid to me
Va me parece un poco chorra
eh I just woke up everything that's
eh acabo de levantarme todo lo que está
happening with us the truth is that until
pasando con noos la verdad es que hasta
now I hadn't talked about the subject because
ahorita no había hablado del tema porque
ad comen I was prohibited from doing so but
ad vinen que se me prohibió hacerlo pero
now that all the [ __ ] is going down
ahora que ya se está yendo toda la
Well I'm going to talk the truth is
[__] Pues voy a hablar la verdad es
that I don't know how to feel about
que no sé cómo sentirme al respecto de
the girls because when what happened to me happened they
las chicas porque cuando pasó lo que me
all turned their backs on me
pasó todas me dieron la espalda
including my long time friends
incluyendo mis amistades de largo tiempo
including Although I helped them but
incluyendo Aunque yo las ayudé pero sin
nevertheless I'm glad that they are finally
embargo Me alegro de que por fin le
destroying all this for these people
estén destruyendo todo esto a esta gente
the truth is that I don't care now all
la verdad es que no me importa ya todas
the opportunities I've had have been
las oportunidades que he tenido me las
absolutely taken away from me so I do
han quitado absolutamente todas así que
n't care anymore I'm going to talk they
ya no me importa la neta voy a hablar
want us to Let's start with the beginning of
quieren que Comencemos con el inicio de
taste like me Mirra and Dr. we started with
gusto como yo mirra y Dr empezamos con
this and how we damaged Dixis gave what
esto y cómo dañamos a dixis dio qué
first of all I want to clarify that the
primero que nada quiero aclarar que la
blacklist does exist it is completely
blacklist sí existe es completamente
real and they applied it to me very hard
real y me la aplicaron a mí muy hard
first of all I cannot monetize my YouTube channel
primero que nada mi canal de YouTube no
because they marked me by
puedo monetizarlo porque me tacharon por
copy so I am the creator of eto I
copia o sea yo soy la creadora de eto yo
kiss Roman Thanks handsome I am eto and they
beso Román Gracias guapo soy eto y me
called me a copy second of all I was
tacharon de copia segundo que nada yo
going to enter an agency, I was going to
iba a entrar a una agencia iba a
work, I was going to be a vtuber for an
trabajar iba a ser vtuber para una
agency that I am not going to reveal the name
agencia que no voy a revelar el nombre
but well you guys already know which one it is
pero pues ustedes ya sabrán Cuál es
because well I and I am very involved in that
porque pues yo and ve muy metida en eso
And that agency uh I received an
Y a esa agencia eh Le llegó un mensaje
anonymous message is what they told me but
anónimo es lo que me dijeron ellos pero
well I don't believe that if they
pues yo no creo eso que si ellos me
debuted me they were going to close all
debutaba a mí les iban a cerrar todas
the opportunities to their
las oportunidades a sus creadoras de
content creators they only had two
contenido ellos solo tenían dos
content creators Only two
creadoras de contenido Solo dos
youtubers and well they told them that they were
youtubers y pues les dijeron que les
going to close the doors and I debuted
iban a cerrar las puertas y me debutaba
so they voted for me they rejected me they
a mí por lo que me votaron me desecharon
told me you know what no because well we don't
me dijeron sabes qué no porque pues no
want to affect our youtubers and
queremos afectar nuestras youtubers y
all that no Okay up to there then I entered
todo eso no Okay hasta ahí luego entré a
another agency you already know which one it is and
otra agencia ustedes ya sabrán cuál es y
guess what happened Drake up told
Adivinen qué pasó Drake up les dijo a
them that if I debuted me they were going to
ellos que si me debutaba a mí les iban a
close their opportunities to some
cerrar sus oportunidades a unos
content creators who were already
creadores de contenido que ya estaban
beginning to relate to the
empezando a relacionarse con los
members of aasu and guess what happened Me  They
miembros de aasu y Adivinen qué pasó Me
sent me on hiatus, the truth is, I don't
mandaron a hiatus la verdad eso no me
care about that Because I love these people very much
importa Porque yo amo mucho a estas
so I decided to do it Not
personas así que yo decidí hacerlo No
because because I Val like no because like
porque porque me Val en plan no porque
accepting wosu's threats
en plan aceptar a las amenazas de wosu
no but because I really love these people
no sino porque realmente a esta gente yo
and I don't want to affect them in
la quiero y no quiero afectarlas de
any way but well, I'm worth it,
ninguna forma pero pues ya me vale
truth Honestly, sorry but I'm
verdad Honestamente perdón pero ya me
worth it then a very dear friend of mine
vale luego a una amiga mía muy querida
with whom I worked Drake up and another
con la que Yo trabajé Drake up y otra
member of osu personally went to
miembro de osu personalmente fueron a
tell them to stay away from me because I
decirles que se alejaran de mí porque yo
was a liar and all my little
era una mentirosa y a todos mis
circle of friends that we had there,
circulito de amigos que teníamos ahí
the whole circle of friends were told
todo el circulito de amigos les dijeron
not to talk to me and they completely banned me
que no me hablaran y me vetaron
from any activity that I
completamente de cualquier actividad que
could see so friends yes the
pudiera a ver así que amigos sí la
blacklist does exist and finally
blacklist sí existe y para finalizar
raku through Twitter I would mention that I
raku mediante Twitter mencionaría que
reported on the official karma account on
reporte en la cuenta oficial de karma de
discord since apparently some
discord ya que al parecer algunas
people had entered their account and I
personas habrían ingresado a su cuenta y
kind of see it as nonsense Let's
como que lo veo una chorrada
see, let's move on to something else
A ver vamos a otra
roldier articles appear from media outlets
roldier aparecen artículos de medios
like la vanguardia as someone who
como la vanguardia como alguien que
manages the agency however he has not
gestiona la agencia sin embargo no se ha
spoken out now man it's that there is no
pronunciado ahora hombre es que no hay
accusation  about him, I mean, there
ninguna acusación sobre él o sea es que
are no accusations about any
no hay ninguna acusación sobre Ninguno
of the creators, no. I mean, what they
de los creadores no O sea de lo que le
're accusing these people of is uh being
están acusando a esta gente es de eh ser
a shitty agency and behaving badly with
una [__] de agencia y portarse mal con
the creators and some of them get kicked out, another one
los creadores y algunos los echa otro
accepts them personally, personally. I
acepta personalmente personalmente me
expected something else,
esperaba otra cosa
uh, I mean, or we're missing something here, but
eh o sea o nos falta aquí algo pero
man, we just saw a 20-
hombre acabamos de ver un vídeo de 20
minute video. This is the
minutos Esta es la
funa. I was seeing this on
funa Es que esto yo estaba viendo en
Twitter like this was good,
Twitter como que esto era bueno la la
Jeffrey epin's island, it
isla de Jeffrey
's shady. Ha. But how. What is
epin es turbio Ja Pero cómo Que es
shady? But how shady. I mean, and I'm
turbio Pero en qué turbio O sea y yo me
asking myself a question, maybe I
hago una pregunta es que a lo mejor me
'm missing information.
estoy perdiendo informa
Okay, what did the girl at the
Vale qué tenía que ver la chica del
beginning have to do with it? The first one we
principio la primera que hemos
saw who said she was being
visto que decía que estaba siendo
abused, but in reality it's not abuse, that it
abusada pero en realidad no es un abuso
had to do
que tenía que ver
with this company,
con con la empresa
Javi. Really, The Strong Ones can't
esta Javi que realmente Los Fuertes no
tell if they can't tell
lo pueden contar si no lo pueden contar
we're not going to find out and I don't know. F to
no nos vamos a enterar y no se F a
anyone, to me, the tips of the isber, you already
nadie a a mí las puntas de los isber ya
know that they're not mine,
sabéis que no son los míos
eh. What's with gref today, from the building,
eh Qué es lo de gref de hoy del edificio
the grandmother, something new came out,
la abuela salio algo
personally, me personally.  it
nuevo personalmente me personalmente me
seems like [ __ ]
parece una [__]
[ __ ] to me I mean it seems like an attempt at a
[__] O sea me parece un intento de
funa eh it looks like Wait wait I don't
funa eh tiene pinta Espera espera no me
want to get ahead of myself it looks like a
quiero adelantar tiene pinta intento de
shitty attempt at funa eh
[__] de funa eh
roldier of the wosu agency that manages
roldier de la agencia wosu que gestiona
eight of its own biters and
ocho biters propios y
Associates tells me luar is a
Asociados me dice luar es una funa
different funa he only funned the founder who was playing
distinta solo funo al fundador que iba
osu's vigilante Ah okay or whatever or whatever
de justiciero de osu Ah vale o sea o sea
or whatever The
o sea El
vigilante The vigilante who has funado
justiciero El justiciero que ha funado a
wosu and has started to bring out things against
wosu y ha empezado a sacar cosas contra
them at the same time is being funado by
ellos a su vez está siendo funado por
a girl who is also
una chica que también lo está
accusing him of abusing her but it's not
acusando de abusar de ella pero no es un
abuse either These are people
abuso tampoco Estos son gente
wanting to funar each other for the [ __ ] face
queriéndose funar por la [__] cara
right I mean I already know these funas
verdad O sea ya me conozco estas funas
no Javi the funa was for the
no Javi la funa fue por el maltrato
workplace abuse they received but let's see let's see let's see let's see let's see
laboral que recibieron pero a ver a ver
this one of
a ver a ver a ver a ver a ver a ver esta
what what what ages are we
de de qué de qué de qué edades estamos
talking about
hablando
here what
aquí de qué edades
mental ages what ages are
mentales de qué edades
we talking about
estamos hablando
here I mean the funa is they treated me very
aquí o sea la funa es me trataron muy
badly at Partner I mean it seems like
mal en el Partner O sea me parece una
[ __ ]
[__]
[ __ ] to me Well, what I found
[__] Bueno pues lo que encontré el día
yesterday was  quite interesting and I do
de ayer fue bastante interesante y es
n't know if you know a certain roldier
que no sé si conocéis a un tal roldier
a youtuber who was
un youtuber que hace tiempo estaba
pretty much finished a while ago is now being
bastante acabado ahora se le está
linked to
relacionando con
hzu as proof of this I found
hzu como prueba de ello Es que encontré
an article in a newspaper called La
un artículo de un periódico llamado La
Vanguardia in which it says that rodier
Vanguardia en el que nombra que rodier
is in uguu Let's see I don't know at what level he's
sí está en uguu A ver no sé a qué nivel
worth but he is related to the
vale pero sí que está relacionado con la
agency so much so that his name has
agencia tanto es así que su nombre ha
been quite famous for those of you who don't
sido bastante sonado para los que no
know riel I'm going to give you a little
conozcáis a riel os voy a poner un poco
context of what he was at least
el contexto de lo que era al menos hace
a few years ago he's a person who is
unos años es una persona que está
really hard up I'm going to have
muy a tomar por culo voy a tener yo aquí
a cameo here but let's see go [ __ ] yourselves
un cameo pero vamos a ver iros a tomar
Why do I have to have a
por culo Por qué tengo que tener un
truck everywhere I mean but [ __ ] off go [ __ ] yourselves I mean
camión en todas partes o sea pero iros a
why but come on we're talking about
qué pero vamos estamos hablando
football any day I mean suddenly
cualquier día de fútbol o sea de repente
I don't know Shakira and piqu throw
yo que sé Shakira y piqu se tiran los
dishes and throw each other's luggage at the
platos y se tiran en el equipaje en la
door of the chalet in Barcelona and
puerta del chalet de Barcelona y sale
Javi oliveira comes out there I'm going to the trial I'm going
Javi oliveira por ahí voy al juicio voy
to the miare trial I mean what the hell is
al juicio de la miare O sea qué [__] es
going on here A  what's this cameo
lo que pasa aquí A qué viene este cameo
is that we can live please we can
es que podemos vivir por favor podemos
live some gossip without me appearing or
vivir algún chisme sin Que aparezca yo o
rather it's The literal eh For the old for
sea está Le literal eh Por lo viejo por
the tasty and for the kameo
lo sabroso y por lo kameo
eh let's
eh
see
a ver
gibel with the girls
gibel con las chicas
s the rare another one that Should Should
s el rar otro que Debería Debería
face some things what I found out
encararse algunas cosas lo que me enteré
about del
de del
roldes it is not seen that he has
roldes no se ve que tiene
friends he has quite a few pedophile friends
amigos tiene amigos bastante pedófilos
but also he likes to minimize
sino que además le gusta minimizar las
women if treating them badly yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes indeed indeed
mujeres si tratarlas mal sí sí sí sí sí
eh rold Deer already called them
eh rold Deer ya las llamaba
explicitly stupid explicitly goes
explícitamente tontas explícitamente va
strong stupid Shut up stupid You what do you
fuerte tontas Cállate tonta Tú qué vas a
know stupid
saber tonta
explicit
explícito
explicit the one who goes as rold of The one who goes as an
explícito el que va de rold de El que va
Ally fista goes goes goes a little goes
de de Aliado fista va va va un poco va
a little of that roll and today today I
un poco de ese rollo y hoy hoy lo
was talking about it with one I was talking about it with a friend of
hablaba con una lo hablaba con un amigo
mine today I was talking to a friend of mine
mío yo hoy le hablaba con un amigo mío
on Twitter he told me it's that
por por md de Twitter me decía es que
those who turn out to be
los que resultan los que van así de ser
more eh what do I know red allies good
más eh qué sé yo rojos aliados buena
vibes and such then they are the worst And it does
onda y tal luego son los peores Y es que
n't fail eh for Fast all these people  It's just that it doesn't
no falla eh for Fast toda esta gente es
fail, man It doesn't fail,
que luego no falla tío es que no falla
dude It doesn't fail It's because they
boludo es que no falla es porque las
insulted them They told them they were
insultaban les decían que eran
useless And when they complained They made
inservibles y cuando se quejaron se
fun of them And while they were sleeping They
mofar de ellas y mientras dormían les
tried to take away their channels
quisieron quitar los canales
Okay But what proof is there of But
vale Pero qué pruebas hay de
what proof is there of
Pero qué pruebas hay de
that Be very careful because although for
ello mucho cuidado porque aunque por
example Rold has always been one to swallow
ejemplo rold siempre ha sido de tragarse
all the accusations made against
todas las acusaciones que le hagan a la
people who dislike him without proof No
gente que él le caiga mal sin pruebas No
In fact, having evidence to the
de hecho habiendo pruebas
contrary, we are not going to do the
contrarias nosotros no vamos a hacer lo
same and so far we have had 42
mismo y yo hasta el momento llevamos 42
minutes of extra mess and I am not
minutos de ex trasto y yo no
seeing absolutely any
estoy viendo absolutamente ninguna
proof I am not seeing absolutely
prueba yo no estoy viendo absolutamente
any proof Okay I understand that the
ninguna prueba vale entiendo que la
accusation is being a piece of [ __ ] Network
acusación es ser una [__] de Network
that they answered them badly Okay We
que les contestaban malamente vale
would have to see what they call an insult But
Habría que ver a qué llaman insulto Pero
well, they insulted them and such to
bueno que las insultaban y tal para
put it
darle de
aside and
lado y
[Music]
[Música]
um that they tried to take away the accounts
em que les intentaron quitar las cuentas
from the badaboom when the
a los badaboom cuando finalizaron los
agreements with her ended Okay What proof is there
acuerdos con ella vale Qué pruebas hay
of that places
de eso lugares
What proof do we have of those
Qué pruebas tenemos de esas
things the funas that has come to light
cosas el funas que ha salido a la luz
with the apparent imminent departure of its
con la aparente próxima salida de sus
talents from the agency seems like it's
talentos de la agencia parece que es el
time  correct to expose roldier And
momento correcto de exponer a roldier Y
although he has already been exposed
si bien ya ha sido expuesto con
previously for carrying out
anterioridad por realizar campañas de
hate campaigns, having groomer friends and not saying
odio tener amigos groomer y no decir
anything until two years later along with a
nada hasta dos años después junto a una
long list of questionable old tweets.
larga lista de tweets viejos
Ugh, the rer twts man,
cuestionables Uf los twts de rer tío
for me this problem starts when
para mí este problema empieza cuando a
a dear friend of mine, an artist recognized
un querido amigo mío artista reconocido
by the community,
por la comunidad
receives some messages on Twitter
recibe unos mensajes por Twitter el
roldier This happened after uploading an art
roldier Esto ocurrió tras subir un arte
tatal let's see what happens with the messages I'm
tatal a ver y qué pasa con los mensajes
talking to you because I saw on funi's
te hablo porque vi en el discord de funi
or perico's discord I want to
o de perico te quiero extender una
apologize for the way because I can't
disculpa por la forma porque no te puedo
send you a private message on discord but I
mandar mensaje privado por discord pero
found on your Twitter that you do @
he encontrado en tu Twitter que haces @
And you use handles of the girls with drawings
Y usas asas de las chicas con dibujos
of their characters I think it's
tal de sus personajes Me parece que está
okay to have content but I think it
bien haer contenido pero creo que ha
could have created something very negative the ways
podido crear algo muy negativo la formas
of providing this that you have
de proporcionar esto que has
chosen for that Sorry but I am going to
elegido por ello Disculpa pero te voy a
remove access to these discord and I
retirar el acceso al discord de estas y
would ask you to delete the drawings that you have
rogaría que eliminase los dibujos que
made mentioning it and using H that
has hecho mencionándolo y usando H que
the community uses to share drawings,
usa la comunidad para compartir dibujos
some of them minor and that you
algunos de ellos menores y que de manera
have used incorrectly, you can
incorrecta has usado puedes volver a
upload it again but I beg you not to use  these
subirlo pero ruego que no usen estos
tags or mentions tag It's like going to
tags o menciones etiqueta Es como ir a
your face to show you something that of
tu cara a mostrarte algo que por
course you might not want Or you might find it
supuesto puedes no desear O puedes
unpleasant, meaning these types of
desagradable o sea este tipo de
drawings
dibujos
are drawing them in a sexual way I don't
son dibujándolas de forma sexual No
understand I think this is a tremendous [ __ ]
entiendo me parece una gilipo tremenda
this fun so far eh forgive me for
esta fun hasta el momento eh perdonadme
telling you if tomorrow we find
que os diga si mañana encontramos cosas
new and stronger things or whatever we will
nuevas y más fuertes o lo que sea las
see them of course and when
veremos por supuesto y cuando salgan
evidence of something super serious comes out
pruebas de algo super grave
eh we will see them okay but so
eh los veremos vale pero hasta el
far I feel like insulting you I feel like
momento me dan ganas de insultarte me
insulting you insult er he is
dan ganas de insultarte insultar er es
a [ __ ]
un [__]
[ __ ] Hello grandpa so long I
subnormal Hola abuelo tanto tiempo yo
always here moderating without donating biceps
siempre aquí moderando sin donar bíceps
I follow your golden rule I only ban those
sigo tu regla de oro solo baneo a los
who go against your guests So
que van contra tus invitados Así que
let's activate those Twitch Partners
vamos a activar esos Partner de Twitch
I want to see those exclusives that I sent you
Quiero ver esos exclusivos que te pasé
do it for the community right man you
hazlo por la comunidad no verdad tío me
sent me some emotes let's see that
mandaste unos emoticones a ver eso que
Ivan is wearing it I have no idea
lo lleva el Iván yo no tengo ni idea
But thanks for the for the bits
Pero gracias por el por los bit
gorgeous thanks for the
guapísimos gracias por los
bits be careful that they funnify you for asking
bits cuidado que te funan por preguntar
about the evidence but it's not that but it's not that they're
por las pruebas pero no es que pero no
going to ask me  by the
es que me vayan a preguntar por las
evidence is that
pruebas es que
really this is all there is no
realmente esto es todo lo que hay no
Lu I mean we understand this is all
Lu o sea entendemos esto es todo lo que
there is we just saw a video that tells you
hay acabamos de ver un vídeo que te dice
eh La La La La The
eh La La La La La funa
complete funa well we will see how
completa bueno iremos viendo cómo
this evolves but for now it
evoluciona esto pero de momento me
seems like a [ __ ] [ __ ] to me It is that in itself it is
parece una [__] chorrada Es que ya en sí
not that
tampoco es
in itself it is not that the
que ya en sí tampoco es que las
accusations are about something super
acusaciones sean sobre algo s super
serious like that they treated them badly that they
grave o sea que las trataban mal que te
treat you badly or they speak to you badly in a place
tratan mal o te hablan mal en un sitio
well you just take it and you leave with your such no And
pues coges y te piras con tu tal no Y
then the fact that the fact that
luego el hecho de que el hecho de que
they want to take away their characters of course That
les quieran quitar los personajes claro
is where the
Ahí es donde estaría los
bad ones would be I mean the bad ones no the
chungos o sea los chungos no lo más
worst thing that I have heard proof there is not
chungo de lo que he escuchado prueba no
only testimony the worst thing that I have
hay solo testimonio lo más chungo de lo
heard is the
que he escuchado es
issue of them taking away their
el el tema de que les quiten las
accounts
cuentas
we will see how it evolves This okay
iremos viendo cómo evoluciona Esto vale
And what evidence is there we will see how
Y qué pruebas hay iremos viendo cómo
this evolves and what evidence comes out but
evoluciona esto y Qué pruebas salen pero
for now caution caution
de momento prudencia prudencia
okay I wanted to take a look at one
vale quería echar un vistazo a un tema
more issue dude it got late because this has
más tío se me ha hecho tarde porque esto
been very long Well in fact they have
ha sido larguísimo Bueno de hecho han
been very long almost  all of today's topics
sido larguísimo casi todos los temas de
no in fact
no de hecho han sido bastante largos
all of today's topics have been quite long but I
todos los temas que de hoy pero que me
have to go man come on I have to go
tengo que ir tío vamos me tengo que ir
no I have to record other content
no que tengo que grabar otros contenidos
eh let's
eh
see what Franco has me
a ver que me tiene por aquí
noted here this is yours Felipe we're
apuntado Franco esta de tuya Felipe esto
going to continue watching this tomorrow man we're
lo vamos a seguir viendo mañana tío lo
going to continue watching this tomorrow I can't take it
vamos a seguir viendo mañana yo no puedo
anymore with my
más con my
life I can't take it anymore with my life but I'm
life yo no puedo más con my life pero
going to do
voy a hacer una
something I'm going to send you guys for the
cosilla Y es que voy a mandaros para el
news what FR and
noticiero lo de FR y
Felipe about ipe we'll talk about tomorrow and it's not gonna matter it
felipes de ipe lo comentamos mañana y no
's just insults to Felipe I already
nada son solo insultos a Felipe Ya ya yo
saw it
lo vi en
live I saw it live but
directo yo lo vi en directo pero de
anyway let's see surra fuela you're going to
todas maneras a ver surra fuela vas a
return to Asturias soon well at the moment I'm
volver a Asturias pronto pues de momento
not thinking bito Why do you
no tengo pensamiento bito Por qué me
ask me at the moment I'm not
preguntas de momento no tengo
thinking honestly
pensamiento la verdad
Not for nothing because the part where I was
No por nada porque la parte donde estuve
I loved the Kanga Doni part the
Me encantó la parte de kanga doni la
truth is that that's a story but
verdad es que eso es un cuento pero
eh what can I tell you I mean I'm going to go to
eh qué te digo o sea voy a voy a
Thailand eh now at the end of the month from
Tailandia eh ahora a final de mes de
Thailand I'm going to Hong Kong
Tailandia me voy a Hong Kong
and I imagine that I won't travel again for a
y me imagino que no viajaré más en un
while I imagine that  I won't travel again
tiempo me imagino que no viajaré más
until summer, not like this, although it's
hasta verano no así aunque sí que es
true that Easter is very
verdad que está la Semana Santa muy
close, I imagine that I won't travel again
cerca me imagino que no viajaré más
for a while, eh, but I don't know, let's see, I
hasta un tiempo eh pero no lo sé a ver
'm going to try to do
voy a intentar hacer una
something that I've done before with the
cosa que lo he hecho antes con la
gentlemen. Cool, so I'm going to try to
señoreros Guay entonces voy a intentar
do it
hacerlo de
again and if I
nuevo y si me
get it right with this, I'm
sale con esto me voy
going to pamper myself. Because I also
con esto me voy a mimir Porque además
have videos already recorded on
tengo vídeos ya grabados en el
telesalseo.
telesalseo
The thing
La Movida
would be to put
sería poner en
the news on premiere
estreno el
and from
y yo de
here I'll do a redirect, it's called,
aquí hag un redirect se llama
eh, from here I'll do a
eh de aquí hago un un
redirect, guys, we're at 50
redirect chicos estamos a 50
subscribers to change numbers,
suscriptores para cambiar de número
eh, I'll leave it there and you guys decide,
eh lo dejo Ahí caer y ya ustedes decidís
okay, redirect, save, okay, in theory
vale redirect guardar vale en teoría
now they're going to send you to the news,
ahora os van a mandar para el noticiero
eh, in theory now they're going to send you to
eh en teoría ahora os va a mandar para
the news, so I'll see you there in
el noticiero así que por allí os veo por
the chat, I'll be watching it
el chat que yo me lo estaré viendo
too, while I finish up a bit
también mientras que termino ya un poco
to sleep,
para dormir
handsome, a huge kiss, a huge kiss,
guapos un beso enorme un beso enorme nos
see you tomorrow, okay, I can't take it anymore, I've
vemos mañana vale que ya no puedo más me
left out two or three topics, maybe what I
he dejado dos o tres temas tal vez lo
can do is that in the afternoon I'll
que puedo que haga que por la tarde me
put on a while or something  We'll see,
ponga un rato o algo ya vemos
okay, a kiss, guys, rest, okay, let's
vale un beso chicos que descanséis vale
see if it
a ver si
works out,
sale
okay
vale